1
00:00:05,755 --> 00:00:07,423
- Hi, guys. JOEY: Hey, Phoebe.
- 大家好 - 菲比

2
00:00:07,632 --> 00:00:08,924
Hey, oh, how did it go?
情况如何？

3
00:00:09,134 --> 00:00:10,175
Um, not so good.
不是太好

4
00:00:10,385 --> 00:00:13,178
He walked me to the subway and said, "We should do this again."
他送我到地铁站 并且说〝我们该再这么做〞

5
00:00:13,388 --> 00:00:16,095
- Ouch. - What? He said, "We should do it again."
什么？他说〝我们该再这么做〞

6
00:00:16,266 --> 00:00:17,307
That's good, right?
那是件好事吧

7
00:00:17,517 --> 00:00:20,602
Uh, no. Loosely translated, "We should do this again," means:
不，简单地翻译 〝我们该再这么做〞是指

8
00:00:20,812 --> 00:00:22,855
"You will never see me naked."
〝你再也看不到我的裸体〞

9
00:00:24,065 --> 00:00:25,274
Since when?
从什么时候开始？

10
00:00:25,483 --> 00:00:28,819
Since always. It's, like, dating language.
一直都是这样，那是种约会语言

11
00:00:29,029 --> 00:00:32,239
You know, like, "It's not you," means, "It is you."
〝那与你无关〞 意思是〝全都是你的错〞

12
00:00:33,616 --> 00:00:34,992
"You're such a nice guy," means:
〝你是个好人〞意思是

13
00:00:35,201 --> 00:00:37,161
"I'm gonna be dating leather-wearing alcoholics...
〝我要跟穿着皮衣的酒鬼约会

14
00:00:37,370 --> 00:00:39,788
...and complaining about them to you."
跟他们抱怨你的事〞

15
00:00:40,623 --> 00:00:43,292
Or, you know, um, "I think we should see other people," means:
〝我想我们该跟别人交往看看〞 意思是指

16
00:00:43,501 --> 00:00:45,002
"Ha, ha, I already am."
〝我已经那么做了〞

17
00:00:46,463 --> 00:00:47,880
And everybody knows this?
大家都知道这些事？

18
00:00:48,089 --> 00:00:50,049
Oh, yeah. Cushions the blow.
对，降低冲击力

19
00:00:50,258 --> 00:00:52,801
Like when you're a kid and your parents put your dog to sleep...
像是你小的时候 爸妈将你的狗安乐死

20
00:00:53,011 --> 00:00:55,429
...and they tell you it went off to live on some farm.
跟你说他逃跑到农场去了

21
00:00:55,638 --> 00:00:58,682
That's funny. No, because, uh, our parents actually did...
那真的很好笑 不，因为我们的爸妈真的…

22
00:00:58,892 --> 00:01:01,393
...uh, send our dog off to live on a farm.
把我们的狗送到农场去

23
00:01:01,603 --> 00:01:04,313
Uh, Ross?
罗斯

24
00:01:05,148 --> 00:01:08,567
Ha, ha. Hello. The Milner's farm in Connecticut?
康涅狄格州的麦纳农场？

25
00:01:08,777 --> 00:01:11,195
The Milners, they had this unbelievable farm.
麦纳夫妇有座超棒的农场

26
00:01:11,404 --> 00:01:13,947
They had horses and rabbits that he could chase.
他们养了马跟兔子 他可以追着他们玩

27
00:01:14,157 --> 00:01:15,991
And it was...
那是…

28
00:01:18,578 --> 00:01:20,954
Oh, my God. Chi-Chi.
天啊，奇奇

29
00:01:23,375 --> 00:01:25,331
Friends S01E03: The One with the Thumb
《老友记》 第一季 第3集：见友弃色

30
00:01:34,219 --> 00:01:36,210
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）

31
00:01:38,223 --> 00:01:40,214
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）

32
00:01:42,227 --> 00:01:44,218
（主演：丽莎·库卓）

33
00:01:48,525 --> 00:01:50,516
（主演：马特·勒布朗）

34
00:01:52,654 --> 00:01:54,645
（主演：马修·派瑞）

35
00:01:56,783 --> 00:01:58,774
（主演：大卫·修蒙）

36
00:02:15,218 --> 00:02:18,095
"So how does it feel knowing you're about to die?"
〝知道自己快死掉时 那是什么样的感觉？〞

37
00:02:17,679 --> 00:02:18,668
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）

38
00:02:18,304 --> 00:02:21,640
Warden, in five minutes my pain will be over.
典狱长，五分钟后我将不再痛苦

39
00:02:21,850 --> 00:02:26,728
But you'll have to live with the knowledge that you sent an honest man to die.
但你得一辈子受到良心谴责 知道自己送一个诚实的人去死

40
00:02:27,939 --> 00:02:29,648
- Hey, that was really good. - Yeah?
- 那真的很不错 - 是吗？

41
00:02:29,191 --> 00:02:30,180
（编剧：杰佛瑞·艾斯多夫  麦克·西考维兹）

42
00:02:29,858 --> 00:02:31,389
- Yeah. - Thanks. Let's keep going.
- 对 - 谢了 继续吧

43
00:02:31,401 --> 00:02:36,238
Okay. "So, what do you want from me, Dimon? Huh?"
好吧， 你要我怎么做？迪蒙

44
00:02:38,783 --> 00:02:42,661
I just wanna go back to my cell, because in my cell, I can smoke.
我只想回我的牢房 因为在我的牢房里，我能抽烟

45
00:02:42,871 --> 00:02:44,621
"Smoke away."
你就抽吧

46
00:02:44,831 --> 00:02:46,412
（导演：詹姆斯·柏洛斯）

47
00:02:52,505 --> 00:02:53,964
Heh.
嘿

48
00:02:57,886 --> 00:03:01,513
I think this is probably why Dimon smokes in his cell alone.
我想这是迪蒙 独自在牢房抽烟的原因

49
00:03:02,557 --> 00:03:04,391
- What? - Relax your hand.
- 什么？ - 手放轻松

50
00:03:04,601 --> 00:03:06,351
Let your wrist go.
手腕下垂

51
00:03:06,561 --> 00:03:07,603
- Not so much.  - Whoa.
- 别垂得那么低  - 哇

52
00:03:07,812 --> 00:03:09,062
Hey.
嘿

53
00:03:10,023 --> 00:03:12,107
All right. Now try taking a puff.
好吧，试着抽一口

54
00:03:12,567 --> 00:03:13,984
Right.
对

55
00:03:15,862 --> 00:03:19,239
- Okay, no, give it to me. - No, no, no. I'm not giving you a cigarette.
- 好吧，不，快给我 - 不，我才不要给你烟

56
00:03:19,449 --> 00:03:22,784
No, it's fine. It's fine. Look, do you want to get this part or not? Here.
没关系的，听着 你要不要这个角色？来吧

57
00:03:23,578 --> 00:03:26,622
All right. Now, don't think of it as a cigarette.
好吧，别当这是香烟

58
00:03:26,831 --> 00:03:30,834
Think of it as the thing that has been missing from your hand.
当它是从你手里不见的东西

59
00:03:31,669 --> 00:03:33,962
When you're holding it, you feel right.
拿着它，你觉得安心

60
00:03:34,172 --> 00:03:36,506
- You feel complete. - You miss it?
- 你觉得圆满 - 你想念它吗？

61
00:03:36,716 --> 00:03:38,342
No, not so much.
不，不是很想

62
00:03:40,094 --> 00:03:42,346
All right. Now we smoke.
好吧，现在抽一口

63
00:03:45,099 --> 00:03:47,601
Oh, my God.
我的天啊

64
00:03:51,398 --> 00:03:54,014
（中央咖啡厅）

65
00:03:55,652 --> 00:03:56,693
No, no, no.
不

66
00:03:56,903 --> 00:04:00,072
They say it's the same as the distance from the tip of a guy's thumb...
他们说那个的长度 跟男人拇指尖

67
00:04:00,281 --> 00:04:01,907
...to the tip of his index finger.
到食指尖的距离一样

68
00:04:08,539 --> 00:04:10,290
That's ridiculous.
那太夸张了

69
00:04:11,709 --> 00:04:13,168
Can I use either thumb?
我可以用另一只手的拇指吗？

70
00:04:15,213 --> 00:04:17,589
All right. Don't tell me, don't tell me.
好吧，别告诉我

71
00:04:18,383 --> 00:04:21,260
Decaf cappuccino for Joey.
乔伊是无咖啡因的卡布奇诺

72
00:04:23,221 --> 00:04:24,972
Coffee, black.
黑咖啡

73
00:04:26,099 --> 00:04:27,307
Latte.
拿铁

74
00:04:29,435 --> 00:04:30,602
And an iced tea.
冰茶

75
00:04:31,229 --> 00:04:34,231
- I'm getting pretty good at this. - Excellent. That's very good.
- 我真的很厉害 - 太好了，非常不错

76
00:04:34,440 --> 00:04:35,857
Good for me.
我太神了

77
00:04:49,622 --> 00:04:52,457
- You okay, Phoebe? - Yeah, no, it's not even worth...
- 你还好吧？菲比 - 对，不，那根本不值得…

78
00:04:52,667 --> 00:04:54,001
It's my bank.
是我的银行

79
00:04:54,210 --> 00:04:55,460
What did they do to you?
他们对你做了什么？

80
00:04:55,670 --> 00:04:57,504
It's nothing, it's just... Okay.
没事，只不过…好的

81
00:04:57,714 --> 00:05:00,340
I'm going through my mail, and I open up their monthly "statement."
我看邮件时打开他们的月报表

82
00:05:00,550 --> 00:05:02,009
Easy.
别激动

83
00:05:04,137 --> 00:05:06,680
And there's 500 extra dollars in my account.
我的账户多了五百块

84
00:05:06,889 --> 00:05:10,142
Oh, Satan's minions at work again.
撒旦的手下又发威了

85
00:05:10,852 --> 00:05:13,312
Yes, because now I have to go down there and deal with them...
对，我得去银行跟他们谈

86
00:05:13,521 --> 00:05:16,732
- What are you talking about? Keep it. - It's not mine.
- 你干嘛说呢？ 留下那笔钱 - 那不是我的钱

87
00:05:16,941 --> 00:05:19,568
I didn't earn it. If I kept it, it would be like stealing.
那不是我赚来的 留下来那笔钱就等于我偷钱

88
00:05:19,777 --> 00:05:23,363
Yeah, but if you spent it, it would be like shopping.
对，把它花掉，可以享受血拼乐趣

89
00:05:24,574 --> 00:05:25,699
Okay. Okay.
好的

90
00:05:25,908 --> 00:05:27,993
Let's say I bought a really great pair of shoes.
假设我买了一双很棒的鞋子

91
00:05:28,202 --> 00:05:30,495
Do you know what I'd hear with every step I took?
你们知道我每跨出一步 会听到什么吗？

92
00:05:30,705 --> 00:05:33,123
"Not mine. Not mine. Not mine."
〝不是我的钱〞

93
00:05:33,333 --> 00:05:36,168
And even if I was happy, okay, and skipping...
即使我开心地飞舞

94
00:05:36,377 --> 00:05:39,546
...I'd hear, "Not mine. Not mine."
我会听到〝不是我的钱〞

95
00:05:39,756 --> 00:05:41,381
We're with you. We got it.
我们同意你的说法，我们了解

96
00:05:41,591 --> 00:05:46,636
Okay, I'd never be able to enjoy it. It'd be like this giant karmic debt.
好吧，我无法享受乐趣 那是一大道德考验

97
00:05:46,846 --> 00:05:49,222
Chandler, what are you doing? Hey.
钱德，你在做什么？

98
00:05:49,432 --> 00:05:51,266
What are you doing?
你在做什么？

99
00:05:54,312 --> 00:05:56,355
Oh, gross.
超恶心的

100
00:05:57,065 --> 00:05:59,399
- What is this? - I'm smoking. I'm smoking. I'm smoking.
- 这是怎么一回事？ - 我在抽烟

101
00:05:59,609 --> 00:06:02,194
I can't believe you. You've been so good for three years.
我不相信，三年来你表现很好

102
00:06:02,403 --> 00:06:04,988
And this is my reward.
这是我的奖励

103
00:06:06,282 --> 00:06:09,659
Hold on a second. Just think about what you went through the last time you quit.
等一下，想想上次戒烟时你吃的苦

104
00:06:09,869 --> 00:06:11,745
Okay, so this time I won't quit.
好吧，所以这次我不戒烟

105
00:06:11,954 --> 00:06:14,456
- Put it out. - All right. I'm putting it out.
- 把烟熄了 - 好吧，我熄了就是

106
00:06:15,750 --> 00:06:17,376
Oh, no.
不

107
00:06:17,585 --> 00:06:19,544
I can't drink this now.
现在我没办法喝咖啡了

108
00:06:23,591 --> 00:06:25,675
All right, I'm gonna go change. I've got a date.
好吧，我要去换衣服，我有约会

109
00:06:25,885 --> 00:06:28,345
Is this Alan again? How's it going?
又是亚伦？情况如何？

110
00:06:28,554 --> 00:06:32,682
It's going pretty good, you know? It's nice and we're having fun.
非常不错，你们知道吗？ 我们相处既愉快又开心

111
00:06:32,892 --> 00:06:34,851
- So when do we get to meet the guy? ROSS: Yeah.
- 我们何时能见到这家伙？ - 对

112
00:06:35,061 --> 00:06:36,812
Let's see, today's Monday...
让我想一想，今天是星期一

113
00:06:37,021 --> 00:06:38,897
- Never. - Come on.
- 永远不可能 - 少来了

114
00:06:39,107 --> 00:06:42,109
- No, not after what happened with Steve. - What are you talking about?
- 不，在史提夫后是不可能了 - 你在胡说什么？

115
00:06:42,318 --> 00:06:45,779
We love Steve. Steve was sexy.
我们爱史提夫，史提夫超性感

116
00:06:48,699 --> 00:06:49,741
Sorry.
抱歉

117
00:06:49,951 --> 00:06:53,078
Look, I don't know how I feel about him yet. Give me a chance to figure it out.
我不知道我对他有什么感觉 给我机会弄清楚

118
00:06:53,287 --> 00:06:54,913
Well, then can we meet him?
然后我们能跟他见面？

119
00:06:55,415 --> 00:06:56,456
No.
不行

120
00:06:56,666 --> 00:06:58,250
Sorry.
抱歉

121
00:07:01,712 --> 00:07:03,171
Why should I let them meet him?
为什么我要让他们跟他见面？

122
00:07:03,381 --> 00:07:06,299
I bring a guy home and within five minutes they're all over him.
我带男人回家 五分钟内他们围着他问个不停

123
00:07:06,509 --> 00:07:10,345
I mean, they're like coyotes picking off the weak members of the herd.
他们像是土狼，专挑弱小猎物下手

124
00:07:11,055 --> 00:07:15,392
Listen, as someone who's seen more than her share of bad beef...
听着 对一个什么倒霉事都遇过的人来说

125
00:07:15,601 --> 00:07:19,396
...I'll tell you, that is not such a terrible thing.
我想那不算是太糟糕

126
00:07:19,605 --> 00:07:22,107
Come on, they're your friends. They're looking out after you.
他们是你的朋友，他们关心你

127
00:07:22,316 --> 00:07:25,652
I know, I know. I wish that once I'd bring a guy home they actually liked.
我知道，我希望 我能带个他们喜欢的男人回家

128
00:07:25,862 --> 00:07:29,573
Well, you do realize that the odds of that happening are a little slimmer...
你知道 如果他们永远不跟这个男的见面

129
00:07:29,782 --> 00:07:31,616
...if they never get to meet the guy.
机率会更小的

130
00:07:33,578 --> 00:07:35,120
Let it go, Ross.
算了吧，罗斯

131
00:07:35,329 --> 00:07:37,080
Yeah? Well, you didn't know Chi-Chi.
是吗？你根本不认识奇奇

132
00:07:41,252 --> 00:07:42,419
MONICA: Do you all promise?
你们都保证吗？

133
00:07:42,628 --> 00:07:45,338
- Yeah, we promise. We'll be good. JOEY: We promise.
- 对，我们保证，我们会很乖的 - 我们保证

134
00:07:45,548 --> 00:07:48,467
Chandler, do you promise to be good?
钱德，你保证会很乖吗？

135
00:07:56,058 --> 00:08:00,270
You can come in, but your filter tip little buddy has to stay outside.
你可以进来，但你的烟得放在外面

136
00:08:06,694 --> 00:08:08,195
ROSS: Hey, Pheebs.
菲比

137
00:08:10,072 --> 00:08:13,241
"Dear Ms. Buffay: Thank you for calling attention to our error.
〝亲爱的布非小姐 谢谢你通知我们犯了错

138
00:08:13,451 --> 00:08:17,579
We have credited your account $500. We're sorry for the inconvenience...
我们将五百块汇到你的账户 抱歉造成你的不便

139
00:08:17,788 --> 00:08:20,665
...and hope you'll accept this football phone...
希望你收下这个足球电话

140
00:08:23,920 --> 00:08:25,921
...as our free gift." Do you believe this?
作为我们的免费礼物〞 你们能相信吗？

141
00:08:26,130 --> 00:08:29,382
Now I have $1000 and a football phone.
现在我有一千块跟这个足球电话

142
00:08:31,052 --> 00:08:33,345
What bank is this?
你在哪家银行开户？

143
00:08:34,847 --> 00:08:36,389
Okay, it's him.
好吧，他来了

144
00:08:38,059 --> 00:08:39,100
- Who is it? ALAN: Alan.
- 哪位？ - 亚伦

145
00:08:39,310 --> 00:08:41,102
Chandler. He's here.
钱德，他来了

146
00:08:44,232 --> 00:08:46,608
Okay, please be good. Please?
好了，拜托你们乖一点

147
00:08:46,817 --> 00:08:48,527
I mean, remember how much you like me.
记得你们有多么喜欢我

148
00:08:50,947 --> 00:08:54,491
Hi. Alan, this is everybody. Everybody, this is Alan.
亚伦，他们是我的朋友 各位，他是亚伦

149
00:08:56,118 --> 00:08:58,370
- Hi. GROUP: Hey.
- 嗨 - 嘿

150
00:08:59,539 --> 00:09:02,457
I've heard so much about all you guys.
我常听到你们的事

151
00:09:08,881 --> 00:09:11,174
MONICA: Thanks, I'll call you tomorrow.
谢谢，明天我再打电话给你

152
00:09:14,262 --> 00:09:15,679
Okay.
好吧

153
00:09:15,888 --> 00:09:19,307
Okay, let's let the Alan-bashing begin.
好吧，开始批评亚伦

154
00:09:19,517 --> 00:09:21,351
Who's gonna take the first shot?
谁要开第一枪？

155
00:09:21,561 --> 00:09:22,727
Hmm?
嗯？

156
00:09:23,145 --> 00:09:24,521
Come on.
来吧

157
00:09:25,439 --> 00:09:26,898
I'll go.
我先来

158
00:09:29,569 --> 00:09:31,987
Let's start with the way he kept picking at...
从他一直挑…

159
00:09:32,196 --> 00:09:33,655
You know, I'm sorry, I can't do this.
对不起，我办不到

160
00:09:33,864 --> 00:09:35,323
Can't do it. We loved him.
我办不到，我们爱他

161
00:09:35,533 --> 00:09:38,118
GROUP: We loved him. - Wait a minute.
- 我们爱他 - 等一下

162
00:09:38,327 --> 00:09:40,412
We're talking about someone that I'm going out with?
我们在谈我的约会对象吗？

163
00:09:40,621 --> 00:09:42,414
GROUP: Yes. - And did you notice?
- 对 - 你们注意到了吗？

164
00:09:42,623 --> 00:09:43,957
GROUP: Yeah.
对

165
00:09:48,504 --> 00:09:51,464
Know what was great? The way his smile was kind of crooked.
你们知道哪一点最棒吧？ 他的笑容有点坏坏的

166
00:09:51,674 --> 00:09:53,675
Yes, yes. Like the man in the shoe.
对，像鞋子里的男人

167
00:09:54,552 --> 00:09:55,677
What shoe?
什么鞋子？

168
00:09:57,096 --> 00:09:58,430
From the nursery rhyme.
童谣里的歌词

169
00:09:58,639 --> 00:10:00,890
"There was a crooked man who had a crooked smile...
〝有个坏男人，带着坏坏的笑容

170
00:10:01,100 --> 00:10:03,727
...who lived in a shoe for a while..."
他在鞋子里住了一阵子〞

171
00:10:06,814 --> 00:10:09,024
So I think Alan...
我想亚伦

172
00:10:09,233 --> 00:10:10,442
...will become the yardstick...
成为标杆

173
00:10:10,651 --> 00:10:13,403
...against which all future boyfriends will be measured.
用来评估你未来所有的男朋友

174
00:10:13,613 --> 00:10:14,779
What future boyfriends?
什么未来的男朋友？

175
00:10:14,989 --> 00:10:17,532
No, no. I think this could be, you know, "it."
不，我想就是他了

176
00:10:17,742 --> 00:10:18,825
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
- 真的吗？ - 对

177
00:10:19,035 --> 00:10:22,495
I'd marry him just for his David Hasselhoff impression alone.
我会嫁给他，因为他的表情 跟大卫赫索霍夫一样

178
00:10:22,705 --> 00:10:25,332
You know I'm gonna be doing that at parties, right?
你们知道我在派对上会怎么做吧？

179
00:10:29,128 --> 00:10:31,630
- You know what I like most about him? - What?
- 你们知道我最喜欢他哪一点吗？ - 什么？

180
00:10:32,465 --> 00:10:35,675
The way he makes me feel about myself.
他让我喜欢我自己

181
00:10:38,512 --> 00:10:40,055
ALL: Yeah.
对

182
00:10:53,277 --> 00:10:54,861
Hi.
嗨

183
00:10:57,198 --> 00:10:58,365
How was the game?
比赛还好吧？

184
00:10:59,742 --> 00:11:01,117
Well...
那个嘛…

185
00:11:01,327 --> 00:11:03,870
- We won! - We won! Thank you! Yeah.
- 我们赢了 - 我们赢了，谢谢，太棒了

186
00:11:04,705 --> 00:11:07,624
Fantastic. I have one question: How is that possible?
太棒了，我有个问题 怎么可能呢？

187
00:11:08,709 --> 00:11:11,002
- Alan. - He was unbelievable.
- 亚伦 - 他太不可思议了

188
00:11:11,212 --> 00:11:14,756
He was like that Bugs Bunny cartoon where Bugs is playing all the positions.
他跟兔宝宝卡通里 每个位置都是兔宝宝一样

189
00:11:14,965 --> 00:11:18,426
But instead of Bugs, it was first base, Alan. Second base, Alan...
但他不是兔宝宝 - 垒，亚伦、二垒，亚伦

190
00:11:22,056 --> 00:11:25,475
I mean, it was like he made us into a team.
他让我们成为真正的球队

191
00:11:25,685 --> 00:11:27,686
Yep. We sure showed those Hasidic jewelers...
对，我们真的 让那些东正教犹太人珠宝商

192
00:11:27,895 --> 00:11:30,522
...a thing or two about softball. - Nice.
- 知道我们多会打垒球 - 太棒了

193
00:11:31,857 --> 00:11:33,441
Can I ask you guys a question?
我能问你们一个问题吗？

194
00:11:33,651 --> 00:11:36,111
Do you ever think that Alan is maybe sometimes...
你们会不会觉得亚伦有时候…

195
00:11:36,320 --> 00:11:40,281
- What? - I don't know. A little too Alan?
- 什么？ - 我不知道，有点太亚伦了

196
00:11:40,491 --> 00:11:43,910
Oh, no. That's not possible. You can never be too Alan.
不，那是不可能的 他不可能会太亚伦

197
00:11:44,120 --> 00:11:48,832
Yeah, it's his innate Alan-ness that we adore.
对，我们爱的是亚伦的内在

198
00:11:49,166 --> 00:11:51,376
- I, personally, could have a gallon of Alan. - Oh!
我就蛮想有一加仑的亚伦

199
00:11:57,383 --> 00:12:00,218
- Hey, Lizzy. - Hey, Weird Girl.
- 莉兹 - 怪女孩

200
00:12:00,428 --> 00:12:03,138
- I brought you alphabet soup. - Did you pick out the vowels?
- 我帮你买了字母汤 - 你把母音挑出来了吗？

201
00:12:03,347 --> 00:12:06,349
Yes, but I left in the Y's. Because, you know, "Sometimes Y."
对，但我留下Y 因为〝有时候非￥不可〞

202
00:12:07,143 --> 00:12:08,768
Um, I also have something else for you.
我还要给你一样东西

203
00:12:08,978 --> 00:12:10,061
Saltines?
盐脆薄饼干

204
00:12:10,271 --> 00:12:12,647
No, but would you like $1000 and a football phone?
不，你要一千块跟足球电话吗？

205
00:12:13,232 --> 00:12:14,607
What?
什么？

206
00:12:15,735 --> 00:12:17,318
Oh, my God.
天啊

207
00:12:17,570 --> 00:12:20,196
- Oh, my God. There's really money in here. - I know.
- 天啊，里面是真的钱 - 我知道

208
00:12:20,406 --> 00:12:22,115
Weird Girl, what are you doing?
怪女孩，你在做什么？

209
00:12:22,324 --> 00:12:24,242
Oh, I want you to have it. I don't want it.
我要你收下它，我不要这些钱

210
00:12:24,952 --> 00:12:27,412
No, no. I have to give you something.
我得给你一样东西 不

211
00:12:27,621 --> 00:12:29,247
No, it's fine. You don't...
没关系的，你不必… 不

212
00:12:29,457 --> 00:12:31,374
Do you want my tinfoil hat?
你要我的锡箔纸帽吗？

213
00:12:31,584 --> 00:12:34,461
No, because you need that. No, it's okay. Thanks.
不，你需要它，没关系的，谢谢

214
00:12:34,670 --> 00:12:36,796
Please. Let me do something.
拜托 让我帮你做些事

215
00:12:37,423 --> 00:12:38,840
Okay, all right. I'll tell you what.
好吧 听我说

216
00:12:39,049 --> 00:12:41,551
You buy me a soda and then we're even. Okay?
你请我喝杯汽水 我们就扯平了，好吗？

217
00:12:42,511 --> 00:12:43,803
- Okay. PHOEBE: Okay.
- 好的 - 好的

218
00:13:45,825 --> 00:13:47,283
Keep the change.
不用找了

219
00:13:48,035 --> 00:13:49,077
Thanks, Lizzy.
谢谢你，莉兹

220
00:13:49,286 --> 00:13:50,453
Sure you don't want a pretzel?
你真的不想吃麻花饼？

221
00:13:50,663 --> 00:13:53,665
- No, I'm fine. Thanks. - See you.
- 不，我不饿，谢谢 - 再见

222
00:13:59,338 --> 00:14:01,214
Huh.
呵

223
00:14:01,590 --> 00:14:02,924
A thumb?
一根拇指？

224
00:14:03,133 --> 00:14:04,676
GROUP: Ew.
呕

225
00:14:05,052 --> 00:14:07,220
I know, I know. I opened it up and there it was...
我知道，我一打开就看到它

226
00:14:07,429 --> 00:14:10,849
...just floating in there, like this tiny little hitchhiker.
漂浮在汽水里 就像是有人要搭便车一样

227
00:14:12,768 --> 00:14:15,395
Maybe it's a contest, you know? Like "Collect all five."
或许这是个比赛 你得收集五根手指

228
00:14:17,940 --> 00:14:19,148
Does, um, anyone wanna see?
有人想看一下吗？

229
00:14:19,358 --> 00:14:20,775
No, thanks.
不，谢谢

230
00:14:21,777 --> 00:14:24,237
- Oh, hey, don't do that. Come on. - Cut that out.
- 别那么做，少来了 - 别闹了

231
00:14:24,446 --> 00:14:25,947
It's worse than the thumb.
那比拇指更糟糕

232
00:14:27,741 --> 00:14:29,534
Hey, this is so unfair.
这太不公平了

233
00:14:29,743 --> 00:14:34,038
- Why is it unfair? - So I have a flaw. Big deal.
- 为什么不公平？ - 我有个缺点，没什么大不了的

234
00:14:34,248 --> 00:14:36,958
Like Joey's constant knuckle-cracking isn't annoying?
乔伊老是按压手指不讨厌吗？

235
00:14:37,167 --> 00:14:39,335
And Ross, with his over-pronouncing every single word.
罗斯说起来会咬文嚼字

236
00:14:39,545 --> 00:14:41,671
And Monica, with that snort when she laughs.
摩妮卡笑的时候会发出怪声

237
00:14:41,881 --> 00:14:44,215
I mean, what the hell is that thing?
我是说那到底是怎么一回事？

238
00:14:46,176 --> 00:14:49,470
I accept all those flaws. Why can't you accept me for this?
我接受那些缺点 为什么你们不接受这样的我？

239
00:14:56,645 --> 00:14:59,898
Does the knuckle-cracking bother everybody, or just him?
按压手指会困扰大家还是只有他？

240
00:15:01,984 --> 00:15:03,359
Well...
那个嘛…

241
00:15:03,819 --> 00:15:05,528
...I could live without it.
没有它，我可以过得更好

242
00:15:06,572 --> 00:15:07,739
Huh.
呵

243
00:15:08,449 --> 00:15:13,119
Well, is it, like, a little annoying? Or is it like when Phoebe chews her hair?
它有点讨厌或跟菲比咬头发一样？

244
00:15:15,956 --> 00:15:19,083
Now, don't listen to him, Pheebs, all right? I think it's endearing.
不，别听他的，菲比，好吗？ 我觉得那很可爱

245
00:15:19,293 --> 00:15:21,544
Oh, you do, do you?
真的吗？

246
00:15:27,593 --> 00:15:30,845
You know, there's nothing wrong with speaking correctly.
发音标准不是件坏事

247
00:15:31,055 --> 00:15:33,848
Indeed there isn't.
一点都没错

248
00:15:36,018 --> 00:15:37,769
I should really get back to work.
我该回去工作了

249
00:15:37,978 --> 00:15:41,064
Yeah, otherwise someone might get what they actually ordered.
不，不然有人会拿到他们点的东西

250
00:15:42,358 --> 00:15:46,694
Oh. The hair comes out and the gloves come off.
真相大白，有人说了实话

251
00:16:02,252 --> 00:16:05,838
Did you ever go out with a guy your friends all really like?
你跟你朋友喜欢的男人约过会吗？

252
00:16:06,215 --> 00:16:07,465
No.
不

253
00:16:08,926 --> 00:16:12,887
Okay. Well, I'm going out with a guy my friends all really like.
好吧，我朋友真的喜欢 跟我约会的男人

254
00:16:14,348 --> 00:16:16,724
We talking about the coyotes here?
你是指那些土狼吗？

255
00:16:16,934 --> 00:16:20,395
Heh. All right. A cow got through.
好吧，有只牛逃过一劫

256
00:16:21,480 --> 00:16:22,772
Can you believe it?
你能相信吗？

257
00:16:22,982 --> 00:16:24,565
It's just, you know what?
那像是…你知道吗？

258
00:16:24,775 --> 00:16:27,735
I just don't feel the thing.
我一点感觉都没有

259
00:16:27,945 --> 00:16:30,530
I mean, they feel the thing. I don't feel the thing.
他们感觉很棒，我一点感觉都没有

260
00:16:30,781 --> 00:16:33,366
Honey, you should always...
甜心，你应该一直…

261
00:16:33,575 --> 00:16:35,535
...feel the thing.
都有感觉的

262
00:16:38,122 --> 00:16:40,915
Listen, if that's how you feel about the guy, Monica, dump him.
听着，如果那是你对那家伙的感觉 摩妮卡，甩掉他

263
00:16:41,125 --> 00:16:43,042
I know, it's just gonna be really hard.
我知道，那真的很难

264
00:16:43,252 --> 00:16:45,128
Yeah, he's a big boy. He'll get over it.
对，他是大人了，他会释怀的

265
00:16:45,337 --> 00:16:50,008
No, he'll be fine. It's the other five I'm worried about.
不，他会没事的 我担心其他五个人

266
00:16:50,801 --> 00:16:52,343
Do you have any respect for your body?
你尊重你的身体吗？

267
00:16:52,553 --> 00:16:54,637
Don't you realize what you're doing to yourself?
你知道你对自己做了什么吗？

268
00:16:54,847 --> 00:16:57,098
Hey, you know, I've had it with you and your cancer...
我受了你们跟癌症

269
00:16:57,307 --> 00:16:59,100
...and your emphysema and your heart disease.
肺气肿及心脏病

270
00:16:59,309 --> 00:17:02,937
The bottom line is, smoking is cool, and you know it.
抽烟很酷，你们知道的

271
00:17:05,441 --> 00:17:06,816
Ahem. Chandler?
钱德

272
00:17:07,026 --> 00:17:08,776
It's Alan. He wants to speak to you.
是亚伦，他要跟你说话

273
00:17:08,986 --> 00:17:10,820
Really? He does?
真的吗？是吗？

274
00:17:12,239 --> 00:17:14,407
Hey, buddy. What's up?
兄弟，有什么事吗？

275
00:17:16,035 --> 00:17:18,369
Oh, she told you about that, huh?
她跟你说了？

276
00:17:19,163 --> 00:17:23,166
Well, yeah. I have one now and then. Well, yeah, now.
对，我偶尔会抽，对，我正在抽

277
00:17:24,084 --> 00:17:25,877
Well, it's not that bad...
没那么糟糕

278
00:17:28,130 --> 00:17:29,672
Well, that's true.
一点都没错

279
00:17:32,384 --> 00:17:36,179
Gee, you know, no one's ever put it like that before.
天啊，没有人那么跟我说过

280
00:17:36,597 --> 00:17:38,723
Well, okay. Thanks.
好吧，谢谢

281
00:17:49,109 --> 00:17:50,151
God, he's good.
天啊，他真的很厉害

282
00:17:51,987 --> 00:17:53,404
If only he were a woman.
可惜他不是女人

283
00:17:53,614 --> 00:17:55,406
Yeah.
对

284
00:18:00,496 --> 00:18:02,121
CHANDLER: Oh, Lamb Chop.
羊排

285
00:18:02,331 --> 00:18:04,957
How old is that sock?
那只袜子有多旧了？

286
00:18:06,001 --> 00:18:09,921
If I had a sock on my hand for 30 years, it'd be talking too.
如果我手里套着袜子三十年 它也会说话

287
00:18:11,465 --> 00:18:16,052
Okay, I think it's time to change somebody's nicotine patch.
好吧，我想有人该换尼古丁贴片了

288
00:18:17,429 --> 00:18:18,846
Hey.
嘿

289
00:18:19,765 --> 00:18:20,807
Where's Joey?
乔伊人呢？

290
00:18:21,016 --> 00:18:24,143
Joey ate my last stick of gum, so I killed him.
乔伊吃掉我最后一块口香糖 我杀了他

291
00:18:25,771 --> 00:18:27,688
Do you think that was wrong?
你觉得那是不对的吗？

292
00:18:29,441 --> 00:18:32,151
- I think he's across the hall. - Thanks.
- 我想他在对面 - 谢谢

293
00:18:32,694 --> 00:18:34,195
There you go.
好了

294
00:18:34,988 --> 00:18:37,240
Ooh, I'm alive with pleasure now.
现在我开心得要命

295
00:18:38,325 --> 00:18:41,077
Hey, Pheebs, you gonna have the rest of that Pop Tart?
菲比，你要吃剩下的果酱馅饼吗？

296
00:18:43,122 --> 00:18:45,915
Does anyone want the rest of this Pop Tart?
谁要吃剩下的果酱馅饼？

297
00:18:47,501 --> 00:18:48,918
Hey, I might.
我想吃

298
00:18:50,003 --> 00:18:51,337
I'm sorry.
抱歉

299
00:18:51,922 --> 00:18:55,383
You know, those stupid soda people gave me $7000 for the thumb.
汽水公司的人 要为拇指的事赔我七千块

300
00:18:55,592 --> 00:18:57,635
- Oh, my God. - Seven thousand dollars?
- 天啊 - 七千块？

301
00:18:57,845 --> 00:19:00,221
And on my way over here, I stepped in gum.
我到那里的路上踩到口香糖

302
00:19:01,640 --> 00:19:03,850
What is up with the universe?
这个世界到底是怎么了？

303
00:19:04,059 --> 00:19:05,143
What's going on?
发生了什么事？

304
00:19:05,352 --> 00:19:08,187
Nothing. I just think it's nice when we're all here together.
没事，我只是想跟大家一起聚聚

305
00:19:08,397 --> 00:19:11,524
It's even nicer when everyone gets to wear their underwear.
如果大家有时间穿内裤会更棒

306
00:19:14,444 --> 00:19:17,155
- Uh, Joey... - Oh.
乔伊

307
00:19:19,741 --> 00:19:21,951
MONICA: Okay. - Oh, come on.
- 好了 - 别这样

308
00:19:22,161 --> 00:19:24,120
Please, guys, we have to talk.
拜托，各位，我们得谈一谈

309
00:19:24,329 --> 00:19:27,123
Wait, wait. I'm getting a déjà vu.
等一下，我有种似曾相识的感觉

310
00:19:27,332 --> 00:19:28,624
No, I'm not.
不，我想太多了

311
00:19:31,503 --> 00:19:33,629
- All right, we have to talk. - There it is.
- 好吧，我们得谈一谈 - 这就对了

312
00:19:37,050 --> 00:19:38,885
Okay, it's about Alan.
好吧，这跟亚伦有关

313
00:19:39,553 --> 00:19:41,846
There's something you should know.
我该跟你们说一件事

314
00:19:43,348 --> 00:19:47,393
Oh, man, there's really no easy way to say this. Uh...
天啊，要这么说并不容易

315
00:19:48,395 --> 00:19:50,813
I've decided to break up with Alan.
我决定跟亚伦分手

316
00:19:55,360 --> 00:19:57,361
Is there somebody else?
你有了别人？

317
00:19:59,781 --> 00:20:01,741
No, no, no. It's just...
不，那只是…

318
00:20:01,950 --> 00:20:04,952
...you know, things change. People change.
感觉会变，人是会变的

319
00:20:05,329 --> 00:20:07,205
We didn't change.
我们没变

320
00:20:09,791 --> 00:20:11,709
So that's it? It's over?
就这样？一切结束了？

321
00:20:13,337 --> 00:20:14,712
Just like that?
就那样？

322
00:20:15,797 --> 00:20:17,548
You know, you let your guard down.
我好不容易打开心房

323
00:20:17,758 --> 00:20:20,843
You know, you start to really care about someone, and I just...
真的开始关心别人，我只是…

324
00:20:24,348 --> 00:20:26,933
- Look, I could go on pretending... - Okay.
- 听着，我可以继续假装… - 好的

325
00:20:27,142 --> 00:20:29,393
No. No, that wouldn't be fair to me...
不，那对我不公平

326
00:20:29,603 --> 00:20:31,395
...it wouldn't be fair to Alan, or to you.
对亚伦或你们都不公平

327
00:20:31,688 --> 00:20:33,689
Yeah, well, who wants fair?
对，谁要公平呢？

328
00:20:33,899 --> 00:20:37,777
I mean, I just want things back, you know, the way they were.
我只希望一切回到从前

329
00:20:39,905 --> 00:20:43,908
- I'm sorry. - Oh, she's sorry. I feel better.
- 我很抱歉 - 她觉得抱歉，我好过多了

330
00:20:45,661 --> 00:20:47,078
I just can't believe this.
我不敢相信

331
00:20:47,287 --> 00:20:51,958
I mean, with the holidays coming up. I wanted him to meet my family.
快过节了，我要他跟我家人见面

332
00:20:53,126 --> 00:20:56,170
I'll meet someone else. There'll be other Alans.
我会认识别人的，还会有别的亚伦

333
00:20:56,380 --> 00:20:57,546
Yeah, right.
对

334
00:21:02,427 --> 00:21:05,972
- Are you guys gonna be okay? - Hey, hey. We'll be fine.
- 你们没事吧？ - 我们会没事的

335
00:21:06,181 --> 00:21:08,808
We're just gonna need a little time.
我们只需要一点时间

336
00:21:09,726 --> 00:21:11,310
I understand.
我了解

337
00:21:16,441 --> 00:21:17,858
Wow.
哇

338
00:21:18,068 --> 00:21:21,988
- I'm really sorry. - Yeah. I mean, I'm sorry too.
- 我真的很抱歉 - 对，我是说我也有点抱歉

339
00:21:22,614 --> 00:21:24,782
But I gotta tell you, I'm a little relieved.
我得说我是松了一口气

340
00:21:24,992 --> 00:21:26,867
- Relieved? - Yeah, well...
- 松了一口气？ - 对

341
00:21:27,077 --> 00:21:29,412
...I mean, I had a great time with you.
跟你在一起，我很开心

342
00:21:30,080 --> 00:21:31,831
I just can't stand your friends.
我受不了你的朋友们

343
00:21:39,172 --> 00:21:42,383
Remember when we went to Central Park and rented boats?
记得我们到中央公园租船的事吗？

344
00:21:44,428 --> 00:21:46,178
That was fun.
那真的很好玩

345
00:21:46,722 --> 00:21:50,266
Yeah. He could row like a Viking.
对，他划起船来就像维京人

346
00:21:55,105 --> 00:21:57,106
- Hi. GROUP: Hi.
- 嗨 - 嗨

347
00:21:59,067 --> 00:22:00,943
So how'd it go?
结果怎么样？

348
00:22:02,029 --> 00:22:04,947
- You know. - Did he mention us?
- 你们知道的 - 他有提到我们吗？

349
00:22:10,370 --> 00:22:12,955
He says he's really gonna miss you guys.
他说他会想念你们的

350
00:22:19,629 --> 00:22:20,838
ROSS: You had a rough day, huh?
你真的很不好过吧？

351
00:22:21,048 --> 00:22:23,841
- Oh, you have no idea. ROSS: Come here.
- 你才不会懂 - 过来

352
00:22:27,471 --> 00:22:29,764
- That's it. I'm getting cigarettes. GROUP: No, no, no.
- 够了，我要抽烟 - 不

353
00:22:29,973 --> 00:22:31,223
I don't care. I don't care.
我不在乎

354
00:22:31,433 --> 00:22:34,560
Game's over. I'm weak. I've gotta smoke. I've gotta have the smoke.
游戏结束，我得抽烟

355
00:22:34,770 --> 00:22:37,355
If you never smoke again, I'll give you $7000.
只要你不再抽烟，我给你七千块

356
00:22:38,607 --> 00:22:40,024
Yeah, all right.
好吧

