1
00:00:02,168 --> 00:00:03,252
PHOEBE: Oh, that's good.

2
00:00:03,420 --> 00:00:05,254
- Okay. All right, Phoebe? - Okay, okay.

3
00:00:05,422 --> 00:00:09,883
If I were omnipotent for a day, I would want, um, world peace...

4
00:00:10,093 --> 00:00:13,178
...no more hunger, good things for the rain forest.

5
00:00:14,264 --> 00:00:15,556
And bigger boobs.

6
00:00:17,100 --> 00:00:19,852
Well, see, you took mine, so...

7
00:00:21,062 --> 00:00:22,438
Chandler, what about you?

8
00:00:22,605 --> 00:00:26,025
If I were omnipotent for a day, I'd make myself omnipotent forever.

9
00:00:26,234 --> 00:00:28,527
Heh. See, there's always one guy.

10
00:00:28,695 --> 00:00:31,405
"If I had a wish, I'd wish for three more wishes."

11
00:00:34,075 --> 00:00:35,534
ROSS & MONICA: Hey, Joey. - Hey, buddy.

12
00:00:35,702 --> 00:00:37,828
What would you do if you were omnipotent?

13
00:00:38,538 --> 00:00:40,831
Probably kill myself.

14
00:00:41,791 --> 00:00:43,250
Excuse me?

15
00:00:43,418 --> 00:00:47,087
Hey, if Little Joey's dead, then I got no reason to live, you know?

16
00:00:49,090 --> 00:00:51,383
Joey, uh, omnipotent.

17
00:00:53,094 --> 00:00:55,054
You are?

18
00:00:55,221 --> 00:00:56,930
Ross, I'm...

19
00:00:57,349 --> 00:00:59,340
Friends S01E04: The One with George Stephanopoulos

20
00:01:08,193 --> 00:01:10,184

21
00:01:12,197 --> 00:01:14,188

22
00:01:16,201 --> 00:01:18,192

23
00:01:22,624 --> 00:01:24,615

24
00:01:26,628 --> 00:01:28,619

25
00:01:30,799 --> 00:01:32,790

26
00:01:47,190 --> 00:01:49,101

27
00:01:49,275 --> 00:01:51,485
How does she do that?

28
00:01:51,653 --> 00:01:54,822
I cannot sleep in a public place.

29
00:01:54,989 --> 00:01:56,323
Would you look at her?

30
00:01:56,491 --> 00:01:57,526

31
00:01:56,491 --> 00:02:00,067
- She's so peaceful. - Yeah.

32
00:02:01,162 --> 00:02:03,622
What? What? Hi.

33
00:02:02,664 --> 00:02:03,699

34
00:02:03,790 --> 00:02:05,958
It's okay, you know. You just nodded off again.

35
00:02:06,126 --> 00:02:08,127
- Oh. - What's going on with you?

36
00:02:08,294 --> 00:02:09,920
- I got no sleep last night. ROSS: Why?

37
00:02:09,838 --> 00:02:10,873

38
00:02:10,088 --> 00:02:13,090
My grandmother has this new boyfriend...

39
00:02:13,883 --> 00:02:17,177
...and they're both kind of insecure in bed, so...

40
00:02:17,345 --> 00:02:18,887
And deaf.

41
00:02:20,682 --> 00:02:24,726
So they're constantly having to reassure each other that they're having a good time.

42
00:02:24,894 --> 00:02:26,937
You have no idea how loud they are.

43
00:02:29,023 --> 00:02:32,109
- You can stay with Rachel and me tonight. - Thanks.

44
00:02:32,277 --> 00:02:34,278
Ninety-five, 96, 97.

45
00:02:34,445 --> 00:02:38,657
See, I told you. Less than 100 steps from our place to here.

46
00:02:38,825 --> 00:02:41,660
You got way too much free time, man.

47
00:02:41,828 --> 00:02:44,913
Hey, there's the birthday boy.

48
00:02:45,081 --> 00:02:46,915
Ross, check it out. Hockey tickets.

49
00:02:47,083 --> 00:02:49,710
Rangers-Penguins tonight at the Garden. We're taking you.

50
00:02:49,878 --> 00:02:51,879
- Happy birthday, pal. - We love you, man.

51
00:02:54,299 --> 00:02:57,217
It's funny, my birthday was seven months ago.

52
00:02:57,760 --> 00:03:00,095
- So? - So I'm guessing you had an extra ticket...

53
00:03:00,263 --> 00:03:03,557
...and couldn't decide which one of you got to bring a date? Huh?

54
00:03:04,142 --> 00:03:06,977
Well, aren't we Mr. The-Glass-is-Half-Empty?

55
00:03:07,979 --> 00:03:09,688
Oh, my God. Oh.

56
00:03:09,856 --> 00:03:11,857
Is today the 20th? October 20th?

57
00:03:12,025 --> 00:03:14,568
- I was hoping you wouldn't remember. - Oh.

58
00:03:14,736 --> 00:03:16,153
What's wrong with the 20th?

59
00:03:16,321 --> 00:03:19,698
Eleven days before Halloween? All the good costumes are gone?

60
00:03:20,992 --> 00:03:23,118
Today's the day Carol and I...

61
00:03:23,286 --> 00:03:26,830
...first consummated...

62
00:03:26,998 --> 00:03:29,791
...our physical relationship.

63
00:03:30,668 --> 00:03:32,461
We had sex.

64
00:03:34,881 --> 00:03:36,715
You know what? I better pass on the game.

65
00:03:36,883 --> 00:03:41,970
I think I'm just gonna go home and think about my ex-wife and her lesbian lover.

66
00:03:42,931 --> 00:03:45,807
The hell with hockey. Let's all do that.

67
00:03:47,518 --> 00:03:49,978
Come on, Ross. You, me, Joey, ice?

68
00:03:50,146 --> 00:03:52,397
Guys' night out? Come on, what do you say, big guy?

69
00:03:52,565 --> 00:03:54,191
Huh? Huh? Huh? 

70
00:03:54,359 --> 00:03:56,777
- What are you doing? - I have no idea.

71
00:03:56,945 --> 00:03:58,195
Come on, Ross.

72
00:03:58,363 --> 00:04:01,156
All right, all right. Maybe it will take my mind off it.

73
00:04:01,324 --> 00:04:03,825
- You promise to buy me a big foam finger? JOEY: You got it.

74
00:04:03,993 --> 00:04:06,912
- All right. - Look, look, look. My first paycheck.

75
00:04:08,289 --> 00:04:12,626
Look at the window. There's my name. Hi, me.

76
00:04:13,753 --> 00:04:15,837
I remember the day I got my first paycheck.

77
00:04:16,005 --> 00:04:19,424
There was a cave-in in one of the mines, and eight people were killed.

78
00:04:21,427 --> 00:04:22,970
Wow, you worked in a mine?

79
00:04:23,137 --> 00:04:25,806
No, I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?

80
00:04:29,227 --> 00:04:31,895
God, isn't this exciting? I earned this.

81
00:04:32,063 --> 00:04:34,523
I wiped tables for it. I steamed milk for it.

82
00:04:34,691 --> 00:04:37,025
And it was totally...

83
00:04:37,193 --> 00:04:39,486
...not worth it.

84
00:04:39,654 --> 00:04:42,364
Who's FICA? Why's he getting all my money?

85
00:04:44,367 --> 00:04:46,660
I mean, what...? Chandler, look at that.

86
00:04:48,204 --> 00:04:50,372
Oh, this is not that bad.

87
00:04:50,540 --> 00:04:52,624
Oh, you're fine, yeah, for a first job.

88
00:04:53,584 --> 00:04:58,922
- You can totally, totally live on this. MONICA: Oh, yeah, yeah.

89
00:04:59,132 --> 00:05:00,382
By the way, great service today.

90
00:05:00,550 --> 00:05:01,675
- Ooh.  - Oh, yeah.

91
00:05:01,843 --> 00:05:03,302
MONICA: Terrific. - It was excellent.

92
00:05:03,511 --> 00:05:06,471
CHANDLER: Unbelievable. And all that milk and stuff? Great.

93
00:05:06,639 --> 00:05:09,224
CHANDLER & JOEY: Hockey. - Hockey. Hockey.

94
00:05:19,902 --> 00:05:22,529
CHANDLER & JOEY: Hockey. - Hockey. Hockey. Hockey.

95
00:05:24,032 --> 00:05:25,615
Rachel?

96
00:05:26,993 --> 00:05:28,035
Oh, my God!

97
00:05:34,167 --> 00:05:37,085
I swear I've seen birds do this on Wild Kingdom.

98
00:05:38,463 --> 00:05:40,255
What are you guys doing here?

99
00:05:40,423 --> 00:05:43,633
Well, we were in the city shopping, and your mom said you work here...

100
00:05:43,801 --> 00:05:46,136
...and it's true.

101
00:05:46,637 --> 00:05:48,013
Yeah.

102
00:05:48,181 --> 00:05:51,475
Look at you in the apron. You look like you're in a play.

103
00:05:54,520 --> 00:05:58,023
God, look at you. You are so big. I can't believe it.

104
00:05:58,191 --> 00:06:00,734
I know, I know. I'm a duplex.

105
00:06:02,278 --> 00:06:03,695
RACHEL: So, what's going on with you?

106
00:06:03,863 --> 00:06:07,491
Well, guess who my dad's making partner in his firm.

107
00:06:10,536 --> 00:06:13,455
And while we're on the subject of news...

108
00:06:16,667 --> 00:06:17,959
Look, look. I have elbows.

109
00:06:25,051 --> 00:06:26,718
Passes it up to Leetch.

110
00:06:26,886 --> 00:06:28,887
Leetch spots Messier in the crease. Here's the pass.

111
00:06:29,055 --> 00:06:30,889
Oh. Oh.

112
00:06:31,557 --> 00:06:35,268
We'll take a time-out while Messier stops to look at some women's shoes.

113
00:06:36,020 --> 00:06:41,024
Carol was wearing boots just like those the night that we first...

114
00:06:41,192 --> 00:06:42,651
...you know.

115
00:06:42,819 --> 00:06:44,403
In fact, she, uh...

116
00:06:44,570 --> 00:06:46,696
She never took them off. Ha, ha.

117
00:06:46,864 --> 00:06:49,366
It's because we... Sorry. Sorry.

118
00:06:50,743 --> 00:06:51,827
I can't believe...

119
00:06:55,123 --> 00:06:57,082
- What? - Peach pit.

120
00:06:57,542 --> 00:06:58,583
Yes, bunny?

121
00:07:00,128 --> 00:07:01,336
Peach pit.

122
00:07:01,504 --> 00:07:04,339
- That night, we, uh, had... - Peaches?

123
00:07:04,507 --> 00:07:06,967
Actually, nectarines, but basically.

124
00:07:08,428 --> 00:07:11,138
- Could've been a peach. - Then we, uh...

125
00:07:11,305 --> 00:07:15,475
Then we got dressed and I walked her to...

126
00:07:15,643 --> 00:07:17,811
...the bus stop.

127
00:07:18,938 --> 00:07:20,313
I'm fine.

128
00:07:20,481 --> 00:07:22,607
Hey, that woman's got an ass like Carol's.

129
00:07:27,447 --> 00:07:30,282
What? I thought we were trying to find stuff.

130
00:07:31,451 --> 00:07:34,119
Oh, come on, you guys. Tell me all the dirt.

131
00:07:34,287 --> 00:07:38,123
Well, the biggest news is still you dumping Barry at the altar.

132
00:07:40,293 --> 00:07:44,004
- All right, let's talk reality for a second. - Okay.

133
00:07:44,172 --> 00:07:46,506
- When are you coming home? - What?

134
00:07:46,674 --> 00:07:47,799
Guys, I'm not.

135
00:07:47,967 --> 00:07:52,637
- Heh. Come on. This is us. - I'm not.

136
00:07:52,805 --> 00:07:56,308
This is what I'm doing now. I've got this job.

137
00:07:56,476 --> 00:07:58,143
Waitressing?

138
00:07:58,311 --> 00:08:01,062
Heh. I'm not just waitressing.

139
00:08:01,230 --> 00:08:03,690
I mean, I'm...

140
00:08:03,858 --> 00:08:05,525
I, um...

141
00:08:06,110 --> 00:08:09,654
I write the specials on the specials board.

142
00:08:09,822 --> 00:08:13,992
And I take the dead flowers out of the vase.

143
00:08:14,202 --> 00:08:19,080
Um, oh, and sometimes Arturo lets me put the little chocolate blobbies on the cookies.

144
00:08:19,248 --> 00:08:22,083
Well, your mom didn't tell us about the blobbies.

145
00:08:33,471 --> 00:08:35,347
MONICA: Hey, Rach. How was it with your friends?

146
00:08:39,602 --> 00:08:43,021
Okay, how would you like some Tiki Death Punch?

147
00:08:43,189 --> 00:08:44,231
What's that?

148
00:08:44,398 --> 00:08:47,359
- Well, it's rum and... - Okay.

149
00:08:50,112 --> 00:08:53,198
We thought since Phoebe's staying over we'd have a slumber party.

150
00:08:53,366 --> 00:08:55,951
We got some trashy magazines, we got cookie dough, we got Twister.

151
00:08:57,453 --> 00:08:59,871
Ooh, ooh. And I brought Operation.

152
00:09:00,039 --> 00:09:04,000
But I lost the tweezers, so we can't operate.

153
00:09:04,710 --> 00:09:07,003
But we can prep the guy.

154
00:09:09,048 --> 00:09:11,258
Rach, it's the Visa-card people.

155
00:09:11,425 --> 00:09:13,718
Oh, God. Ask them what they want.

156
00:09:13,886 --> 00:09:17,222
Could you please tell me what this is in reference to?

157
00:09:18,099 --> 00:09:19,140
Yes, hold on.

158
00:09:19,308 --> 00:09:21,893
Um, they say there's been unusual activity on your account.

159
00:09:22,061 --> 00:09:26,314
- But I haven't used my card in weeks. - That is the unusual activity.

160
00:09:28,401 --> 00:09:30,652
They just wanna see if you're okay.

161
00:09:30,820 --> 00:09:32,779
They wanna know if I'm okay?

162
00:09:32,947 --> 00:09:35,282
Okay, they wanna know if I'm okay. Okay, let's see.

163
00:09:35,449 --> 00:09:38,868
Well, let's see. The FICA guys took all my money.

164
00:09:39,036 --> 00:09:42,914
Everyone I know is either getting married or getting pregnant or getting promoted...

165
00:09:43,082 --> 00:09:44,583
...and I'm getting coffee.

166
00:09:44,750 --> 00:09:46,876
And it's not even for me.

167
00:09:47,044 --> 00:09:50,630
So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay, then you can tell them I'm okay. Okay?

168
00:09:53,509 --> 00:09:56,845
Uh, Rachel has left the building.

169
00:09:57,888 --> 00:10:01,516
- Can you call back? - All right. Come on.

170
00:10:02,059 --> 00:10:04,603
Let's play Twister.

171
00:10:06,523 --> 00:10:07,558

172
00:10:07,732 --> 00:10:10,348

173
00:10:12,987 --> 00:10:16,114
- Sorry. - Sorry, sorry, sorry.

174
00:10:16,282 --> 00:10:17,657
Uh-oh.

175
00:10:17,825 --> 00:10:20,577
What? There was ice there that night with Carol?

176
00:10:20,745 --> 00:10:24,831
Plastic seats? Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?

177
00:10:25,750 --> 00:10:29,210
No, actually, I was just saying it looks like we're not sitting together.

178
00:10:29,378 --> 00:10:33,131
But now that you mention it, there was ice there that night.

179
00:10:33,841 --> 00:10:36,259
It was the first frost.

180
00:10:36,427 --> 00:10:39,346
- We were... - Sit. Just sit down. Sit.

181
00:10:39,513 --> 00:10:40,805
You should feel great.

182
00:10:40,973 --> 00:10:43,141
You're doing this amazing independent thing.

183
00:10:43,309 --> 00:10:45,435
Monica, what is so amazing?

184
00:10:45,603 --> 00:10:50,065
I gave up like everything. And for what?

185
00:10:50,232 --> 00:10:51,775
You are just like Jack.

186
00:10:52,443 --> 00:10:53,735
Jack from downstairs?

187
00:10:54,362 --> 00:10:57,405
No, Jack and the Beanstalk.

188
00:10:57,615 --> 00:11:00,367
- Ah, the other Jack. - Yeah, right.

189
00:11:00,534 --> 00:11:04,162
See, he gave up something, but then he got those magic beans.

190
00:11:04,330 --> 00:11:08,541
And then he woke up and there was this big plant...

191
00:11:08,709 --> 00:11:12,170
...outside of his window, full of possibilities and stuff.

192
00:11:12,338 --> 00:11:16,007
And he lived in a village, and you live in the Village.

193
00:11:16,467 --> 00:11:20,011
Okay, but, Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up a cow.

194
00:11:20,179 --> 00:11:22,472
I gave up an orthodontist.

195
00:11:22,640 --> 00:11:25,016
Okay, I know I didn't love him, but...

196
00:11:25,184 --> 00:11:27,936
Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.

197
00:11:28,396 --> 00:11:31,314
But, see, it was a plan, you know? It was clear.

198
00:11:31,482 --> 00:11:34,693
Everything was figured out, and now everything's just kind of like...

199
00:11:34,860 --> 00:11:36,903
- Flupie? - Yeah.

200
00:11:38,280 --> 00:11:41,157
You're not the only one. We don't know where we're going.

201
00:11:41,325 --> 00:11:44,077
You gotta figure, at some point, it's gonna come together...

202
00:11:44,245 --> 00:11:47,080
...and it's just gonna be "unflupie."

203
00:11:47,248 --> 00:11:48,832
Yeah, like that's a word.

204
00:11:52,169 --> 00:11:55,505
Okay, but, Monica, what if it doesn't come together?

205
00:11:57,675 --> 00:11:59,300
Pheebs?

206
00:12:00,219 --> 00:12:03,680
Well, because you just... I don't like this question.

207
00:12:04,890 --> 00:12:08,435
Okay, see? See, you guys? What if we don't get magic beans?

208
00:12:08,602 --> 00:12:11,271
I mean, what if all we've got are...

209
00:12:11,439 --> 00:12:13,356
...beans?

210
00:12:16,944 --> 00:12:20,196
Get him! Get him! Get him!

211
00:12:20,364 --> 00:12:23,575
Get... Yes! You're not laughing now, are you, pal?

212
00:12:23,743 --> 00:12:27,370
That's all you need, a bunch of toothless guys hitting each other with sticks.

213
00:12:27,538 --> 00:12:29,831
Pass it. Pass it.

214
00:12:29,999 --> 00:12:33,877
CHANDLER: He's open, he's open. Shoot it, shoot it, shoot it!

215
00:12:36,547 --> 00:12:38,548
- Whoa. Oh.  - Whoa.

216
00:12:39,842 --> 00:12:43,178
- Hey, look, we're on that TV thing. - Ooh, ooh, ooh.

217
00:12:43,345 --> 00:12:46,014
- I got it! - Hey, hey, we got it! Hey!

218
00:12:54,649 --> 00:12:56,514

219
00:12:57,109 --> 00:12:58,777
Excuse me.

220
00:12:58,944 --> 00:13:03,281
It says to call this number if you're not completely satisfied with this candy bar.

221
00:13:07,328 --> 00:13:10,413
Well, I'm not completely satisfied.

222
00:13:11,040 --> 00:13:12,665
Listen, it's kind of an emergency.

223
00:13:12,833 --> 00:13:15,293
I guess you'd know that, or we'd be in the predicament room.

224
00:13:18,798 --> 00:13:21,633
Hold on. Fill these out. Sit over there.

225
00:13:21,801 --> 00:13:24,010
ROSS: Look, I don't wanna make any trouble, okay?

226
00:13:24,178 --> 00:13:28,473
But I'm in a lot of pain here, all right? My face is dented.

227
00:13:28,641 --> 00:13:32,894
- Well, you'll have to wait your turn. - Well, how long do you think it'll be?

228
00:13:33,312 --> 00:13:34,896
Any minute now.

229
00:13:37,650 --> 00:13:40,151
ROSS: Hey, listen... Ooh.

230
00:13:43,739 --> 00:13:48,827
<i>♪ I wake up and I start to cry</i>

231
00:13:48,994 --> 00:13:50,954
<i>♪ Ain't no hope in...</i>

232
00:13:51,121 --> 00:13:56,209
Oh. I'm so sorry, you guys. I didn't mean to bring you down.

233
00:13:56,377 --> 00:13:58,753
No, you were right.

234
00:13:58,921 --> 00:14:01,714
I don't have a plan.

235
00:14:03,884 --> 00:14:04,926
MAN: Pizza guy.

236
00:14:05,094 --> 00:14:07,011
- Thank God. - Food.

237
00:14:07,179 --> 00:14:09,389
- Phoebe? PHOEBE: What?

238
00:14:09,557 --> 00:14:13,810
- Do you have a plan? - I don't even have a "pla."

239
00:14:16,355 --> 00:14:18,606
Hi. One mushroom, green pepper and onion?

240
00:14:19,149 --> 00:14:22,819
No, no, no. That's not what we ordered.

241
00:14:22,987 --> 00:14:27,115
We ordered a fat-free crust with extra cheese.

242
00:14:29,827 --> 00:14:32,328
- Wait, you're not G. Stephanopoulos? - No.

243
00:14:32,496 --> 00:14:35,623
- Oh, man. My dad's gonna kill me. - Wait.

244
00:14:35,791 --> 00:14:39,127
Did you say G. Stephanopoulos?

245
00:14:39,295 --> 00:14:41,921
Yeah, this one goes across the street. I must have given him yours.

246
00:14:42,089 --> 00:14:44,382
Oh, bonehead. Bonehead.

247
00:14:45,009 --> 00:14:49,888
Wait, was this a small Mediterranean guy with curiously intelligent good looks?

248
00:14:50,806 --> 00:14:52,265
Yeah, that sounds about right.

249
00:14:52,433 --> 00:14:56,477
- Was he wearing a stunning blue suit? - And a power tie?

250
00:14:57,313 --> 00:14:59,105
No, pretty much just a towel.

251
00:14:59,273 --> 00:15:01,149
- Oh, God. - Oh. Oh.

252
00:15:01,317 --> 00:15:03,443
- Oh, my God. - You want me to take this back?

253
00:15:03,611 --> 00:15:07,447
What? Are you nuts? We've got George Stephanopoulos' pizza.

254
00:15:09,074 --> 00:15:10,533
Here.

255
00:15:12,036 --> 00:15:13,703
- Uh, Pheebs? - Yeah?

256
00:15:13,871 --> 00:15:15,330
Who's George Snuffleupagus?

257
00:15:18,042 --> 00:15:19,417
That's Big Bird's friend.

258
00:15:22,713 --> 00:15:23,755
I see pizza.

259
00:15:23,923 --> 00:15:26,049
PHOEBE: Oh, I wanna see. Let me see. Let me see.

260
00:15:26,216 --> 00:15:28,259
Hello? Who are we spying on?

261
00:15:28,427 --> 00:15:31,638
You know the White House adviser? Clinton's campaign guy?

262
00:15:31,805 --> 00:15:35,224
The one with the great hair, sexy smile, really cute butt?

263
00:15:35,392 --> 00:15:39,395
Oh, him. The little guy. Oh, I love him.

264
00:15:39,605 --> 00:15:42,732
Ooh. Oh, wait. Wait, I see a woman.

265
00:15:42,900 --> 00:15:44,984
Tell me it's his mother.

266
00:15:45,152 --> 00:15:47,820
- Definitely not his mother. - Oh, no.

267
00:15:48,030 --> 00:15:50,073
Oh, wait, she's walking across the floor.

268
00:15:50,240 --> 00:15:52,992
She's walking, she's walking.

269
00:15:53,160 --> 00:15:56,746
She's going for the pizza. Hey, that's not for you, bitch!

270
00:16:01,835 --> 00:16:04,921
WOMAN [OVER PA]: Dr. Max to Center 456.

271
00:16:05,089 --> 00:16:08,841
Dr. Max to Center 456.

272
00:16:11,762 --> 00:16:14,097
Excuse me. We've been here for over an hour...

273
00:16:14,264 --> 00:16:16,683
...and people less sick than my friend have gone in.

274
00:16:16,850 --> 00:16:19,936
I mean, that guy with the toe thing? Who's he sleeping with?

275
00:16:23,273 --> 00:16:26,025
Oh, come on, Dora. Don't be mad.

276
00:16:26,193 --> 00:16:28,736
I know we both said some things...

277
00:16:30,030 --> 00:16:31,406
...we didn't mean...

278
00:16:31,573 --> 00:16:34,867
...but that doesn't mean we still don't love each other.

279
00:16:35,369 --> 00:16:37,996
You know, I feel like I've lost her.

280
00:16:42,001 --> 00:16:43,918
- Lights still out? - Yeah.

281
00:16:44,086 --> 00:16:46,004
Well, maybe they're napping.

282
00:16:46,171 --> 00:16:48,965
Heh. Please. They're having sex.

283
00:16:49,133 --> 00:16:50,633
MONICA & PHOEBE: Shut up.

284
00:16:55,931 --> 00:16:59,267
So, what do you think George is like?

285
00:16:59,435 --> 00:17:01,811
- I think he's shy. - Oh, yeah?

286
00:17:01,979 --> 00:17:04,605
Yeah. I think you have to draw him out.

287
00:17:04,773 --> 00:17:08,735
And then when you do, he's a preppy animal.

288
00:17:11,905 --> 00:17:13,364
Come on.

289
00:17:13,615 --> 00:17:16,868
I remember the moonlight coming in through the open window...

290
00:17:17,036 --> 00:17:20,538
...and her face had the most incredible glow.

291
00:17:20,706 --> 00:17:23,916
Yes, the moon, the glow, the magical feeling.

292
00:17:24,084 --> 00:17:25,126
You did this part.

293
00:17:25,294 --> 00:17:28,337
Could I get some painkillers over here, please?

294
00:17:29,006 --> 00:17:32,759
He's right, enough already. What is the big deal about today?

295
00:17:32,926 --> 00:17:35,595
So you slept with her for the first time. So what?

296
00:17:35,763 --> 00:17:38,181
You slept with her for seven years after that.

297
00:17:39,683 --> 00:17:41,809
It's just a little more complicated than that.

298
00:17:41,977 --> 00:17:44,771
What? What is it? That she left you? That she likes women?

299
00:17:44,938 --> 00:17:47,106
That she left you for a woman that likes women?

300
00:17:47,274 --> 00:17:48,316
A little louder.

301
00:17:48,484 --> 00:17:51,652
There's a man on the 12th floor in a coma who didn't quite hear you.

302
00:17:55,282 --> 00:17:56,365
Then what?

303
00:17:57,493 --> 00:18:00,161
My first time with Carol was...

304
00:18:00,329 --> 00:18:01,370
Was my...

305
00:18:03,624 --> 00:18:05,041
What?

306
00:18:07,586 --> 00:18:10,379
It was my first...

307
00:18:10,547 --> 00:18:11,964
...time.

308
00:18:13,008 --> 00:18:14,842
With Carol?

309
00:18:19,640 --> 00:18:20,973
Oh.

310
00:18:21,683 --> 00:18:24,519
So in your whole life, you've only been with one?

311
00:18:24,686 --> 00:18:25,937
Oh.

312
00:18:26,814 --> 00:18:30,817
Oh, boy. Hockey was a big mistake.

313
00:18:31,276 --> 00:18:34,445
There's a whole bunch of stuff we could've done tonight.

314
00:18:35,864 --> 00:18:38,241
Okay. Okay, I got one.

315
00:18:38,909 --> 00:18:43,538
Do you remember that vegetarian pâté that I made that you loved so much?

316
00:18:43,705 --> 00:18:44,747
Uh-huh.

317
00:18:46,125 --> 00:18:49,252
Well, unless goose is a vegetable...

318
00:18:49,461 --> 00:18:52,630
- Oh! Oh!  MONICA & RACHEL: Ha-ha-ha.

319
00:18:52,798 --> 00:18:54,340
Okay, fine, fine.

320
00:18:54,508 --> 00:18:57,135
Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with Jason Hurley.

321
00:18:57,594 --> 00:19:01,389
- What? You slept with Jason? - You had already broken up.

322
00:19:01,557 --> 00:19:04,058
- How long? - Just a couple hours.

323
00:19:04,226 --> 00:19:06,227
Oh, that's nice.

324
00:19:06,395 --> 00:19:08,855
Okay, okay, okay, I got one.

325
00:19:10,858 --> 00:19:11,899
Anyway.

326
00:19:12,067 --> 00:19:15,778
The valentine Tommy Rollerson left in your locker was really from me.

327
00:19:16,446 --> 00:19:17,488
Excuse me?

328
00:19:18,198 --> 00:19:21,826
Oh, hello? Like he was really gonna send you one.

329
00:19:24,288 --> 00:19:26,414
She was a big girl.

330
00:19:28,083 --> 00:19:29,125
Really?

331
00:19:29,293 --> 00:19:34,589
Well, at least big girls don't pee in their pants in seventh grade.

332
00:19:34,756 --> 00:19:37,550
I was laughing. You made me laugh.

333
00:19:37,718 --> 00:19:40,344
Oh, my God. There he is. There he is. There he is.

334
00:19:40,512 --> 00:19:43,973
- Where? - Right where we've been looking all night.

335
00:19:44,141 --> 00:19:47,101
- Oh, he's so cute. - Oh, George, baby, drop the towel.

336
00:19:47,269 --> 00:19:49,520
- Come on, drop the towel. RACHEL & PHOEBE: Drop the towel.

337
00:19:49,688 --> 00:19:51,564
MONICA: Please drop the towel. Drop it.

338
00:19:52,024 --> 00:19:53,399
ALL: Wow.

339
00:19:56,904 --> 00:20:01,991
Man, can you believe he's only had sex with one woman?

340
00:20:02,868 --> 00:20:04,410
I think it's great.

341
00:20:04,578 --> 00:20:09,040
You know, it's sweet. It's romantic.

342
00:20:09,958 --> 00:20:11,083
Really?

343
00:20:11,251 --> 00:20:14,420
No, are you kidding? The guy's a freak. I judge him.

344
00:20:14,588 --> 00:20:15,880
- Hey, man. - Hey, buddy.

345
00:20:16,048 --> 00:20:17,882
ROSS: Ah? Ah?

346
00:20:20,427 --> 00:20:21,719
Oh.

347
00:20:21,887 --> 00:20:23,554
That's attractive.

348
00:20:25,641 --> 00:20:27,683
Oh, I thought you were great in Silence of the Lambs.

349
00:20:31,104 --> 00:20:34,398
Oh, come on, admit it, all things considered, you had fun tonight.

350
00:20:34,566 --> 00:20:35,733
Fun? Where was the fun?

351
00:20:35,901 --> 00:20:38,486
Tell me specifically, which part was the fun part?

352
00:20:38,654 --> 00:20:39,904
Where's my puck?

353
00:20:40,072 --> 00:20:42,865
- Oh. The kid has it. - The kid?

354
00:20:43,700 --> 00:20:46,786
Ahem. Excuse me, uh, that's my puck.

355
00:20:46,954 --> 00:20:50,539
I found it. Finders keepers, losers weepers.

356
00:20:54,044 --> 00:20:56,087
You gotta do it, man.

357
00:20:57,089 --> 00:20:59,966
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm rubber, you're glue. Whatever you...

358
00:21:00,133 --> 00:21:02,218
I can't do it.

359
00:21:02,386 --> 00:21:05,513
- Listen, uh, give me back my puck. - No.

360
00:21:05,681 --> 00:21:06,722
- Yes, how about? - No.

361
00:21:06,890 --> 00:21:08,849
- No, come here. Just give me my puck. - No, no, no.

362
00:21:09,017 --> 00:21:10,977
SIZEMORE: Hey, no roughhousing in my ER.

363
00:21:11,144 --> 00:21:12,770
Give me my puck! Unh.

364
00:21:18,193 --> 00:21:20,736
Now, that was fun.

365
00:21:26,410 --> 00:21:28,035
ROSS: Okay, Monica.

366
00:21:28,203 --> 00:21:30,746
Right foot, red.

367
00:21:30,956 --> 00:21:34,375
Could've played Monopoly, but no.

368
00:21:40,674 --> 00:21:42,216
Thanks.

369
00:21:48,056 --> 00:21:51,142
Okay, Pheebs. Right hand, blue.

370
00:21:53,854 --> 00:21:56,188
- Good. JOEY: Hmm?

371
00:22:00,986 --> 00:22:02,486
Hello?

372
00:22:03,030 --> 00:22:06,907
- Oh. Rachel, it's the Visa-card people. RACHEL: Oh, okay. Will you take my place?

373
00:22:07,075 --> 00:22:08,993
All right. Yes, this is Rachel.

374
00:22:09,202 --> 00:22:10,661
RACHEL: No. - Oh.

375
00:22:12,914 --> 00:22:13,956
Hello?

376
00:22:14,166 --> 00:22:18,044
Oh, yeah. No, I know. I haven't been using it much.

377
00:22:18,211 --> 00:22:21,756
Oh, well, thanks, but I'm okay, really.

378
00:22:21,923 --> 00:22:23,299
To the green, to the green.

379
00:22:23,467 --> 00:22:24,675
MONICA: Oh, no. - To the green.

380
00:22:24,843 --> 00:22:27,178
I've got magic beans.

381
00:22:29,473 --> 00:22:30,973
No, no, never mind.

382
00:22:31,141 --> 00:22:32,558
CHANDLER: To the left. To the left.

383
00:22:35,228 --> 00:22:37,396
I'm fine.

