1
00:00:02,711 --> 00:00:04,878
Would you let it go? It's not a big deal.
得了，那没什么大不了的

2
00:00:05,130 --> 00:00:06,880
ROSS: Not a big deal? It's amazing.
没什么？简直是太神奇了

3
00:00:07,132 --> 00:00:10,009
You just reach in, there's one little maneuver, and bam!
只要把手伸进去弄一弄

4
00:00:10,218 --> 00:00:12,428
A bra. Right out the sleeve.
一件胸罩 就直接从袖子里出来

5
00:00:12,846 --> 00:00:14,179
As far as I'm concerned...
据我所知，这种事

6
00:00:14,431 --> 00:00:17,683
...there is nothing a guy can do that comes close. Right?
男人根本就做不来，对吧？

7
00:00:17,934 --> 00:00:20,894
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
拜托！你们男人可以站着小便

8
00:00:21,146 --> 00:00:23,355
We can? Okay, I'm trying that.
我们可以吗？ 好，我会试试

9
00:00:25,150 --> 00:00:26,692
You know what blows my mind?
知道我想到什么了吗？

10
00:00:26,901 --> 00:00:30,154
Women can see breasts anytime they want.
女人随时可以看到胸部

11
00:00:32,365 --> 00:00:34,533
You just look down, and there they are.
只要往下一看 就在那里

12
00:00:34,743 --> 00:00:37,286
How you get any work done is beyond me.
真不懂你们哪有办法 专心做事

13
00:00:38,788 --> 00:00:42,291
What I don't get is the way guys can do so many mean things...
我知道了…我不懂男人怎能 做出许多残忍的事情…

14
00:00:42,500 --> 00:00:43,917
...and then not even care.
却完全不在乎

15
00:00:50,800 --> 00:00:52,926
Multiple orgasms!
多重性高潮！

16
00:00:57,182 --> 00:00:59,298
Friends S01E05: The One with the East German Laundry Detergent
《老友记》 第一季 第5集：东德进口的洗衣粉

17
00:01:08,193 --> 00:01:10,184
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）

18
00:01:12,197 --> 00:01:14,188
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）

19
00:01:16,159 --> 00:01:18,150
（主演：丽莎·库卓）

20
00:01:22,457 --> 00:01:24,448
（主演：马特·勒布朗）

21
00:01:26,628 --> 00:01:28,619
（主演：马修·派瑞）

22
00:01:30,757 --> 00:01:32,748
（主演：大卫·修蒙）

23
00:01:46,440 --> 00:01:48,351
（中央咖啡厅）

24
00:01:48,733 --> 00:01:50,526
So Saturday night, the big night.
周六夜 大日子！

25
00:01:50,777 --> 00:01:53,904
Date night! Saturday night. Saturday night!
约会的日子！ 周六夜，周六夜！

26
00:01:55,990 --> 00:01:58,283
- No plans, huh? - Not a one.
- 你没节目，对吧？ - 一个也没有！

27
00:01:59,410 --> 00:02:01,328
Not even, say, breaking up with Janice?
连跟珍妮丝分手的计划也没有？

28
00:02:00,412 --> 00:02:01,401
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）

29
00:02:01,579 --> 00:02:03,831
Oh, right, right. Shut up.
对，对，闭嘴

30
00:02:05,667 --> 00:02:08,460
Chandler, nobody likes breaking up with someone.
钱德，没人喜欢跟别人分手

31
00:02:07,502 --> 00:02:08,537
（编剧：杰夫·葛林斯坦  杰夫·史特劳斯）

32
00:02:08,753 --> 00:02:12,297
- You just gotta do it. - I know. But it's just so hard.
- 只是你非做不可 - 我知道，不过真的很难

34
00:02:12,382 --> 00:02:13,417
（导演：帕蜜拉·佛莱曼）

33
00:02:13,592 --> 00:02:15,503
You're sitting with her. She has no idea what's happening.
你就跟她坐在一起 她浑然不觉

34
00:02:15,760 --> 00:02:18,220
You finally get up the courage to do it.
终于你鼓起勇气 开始行动

35
00:02:18,471 --> 00:02:21,765
There's that awkward moment when you've handed her the note.
当你把纸条传给她时 气氛很僵

36
00:02:25,478 --> 00:02:27,729
Why do you have to break up with her?
你干嘛非得跟她分手不可？

37
00:02:27,939 --> 00:02:30,566
Be a man. Just stop calling.
像个男人，不要再打电话就好了

38
00:02:33,153 --> 00:02:35,112
If you want, I'll do it with you.
如果你需要的话 我可以跟你一起做

39
00:02:35,655 --> 00:02:38,991
Thanks, but she'd feel like we were ganging up on her.
谢谢，不过她会觉得 我们在联合起来对付她

40
00:02:39,242 --> 00:02:41,869
I mean you break up with Janice. I'll break up with Tony.
不，我是说是你甩珍妮丝 我甩东尼

41
00:02:42,120 --> 00:02:43,537
You're breaking up with Tony?
你要跟东尼分手？

42
00:02:43,788 --> 00:02:46,456
I know. He's sweet, but it's just not fun anymore.
他很甜，不过已经不好玩了

43
00:02:46,708 --> 00:02:50,002
I don't know if it's me or his hunger strike. I don't know.
我不晓得原因在于我 或在于他的绝食

44
00:02:52,380 --> 00:02:53,881
Does anybody want anything else?
你们还要点些什么吗？

45
00:02:54,132 --> 00:02:58,635
Yeah. Last week you had a wonderful nutty, chocolate-y, kind of cake-y pie thing that...
对了，你们上礼拜有一种有很好吃的 核桃巧克力的蛋糕或派的一种…

46
00:03:00,221 --> 00:03:01,805
Nothing. I'm fine.
不用了，我不饿

47
00:03:02,015 --> 00:03:03,004
（《自行车》）

48
00:03:04,434 --> 00:03:06,393
What's the matter? Why so scrunchie?
怎么了？ 干嘛苦瓜脸？

49
00:03:07,020 --> 00:03:10,063
It's my father. He wants to give me a Mercedes convertible.
我爸要给我一辆宾士敞篷

50
00:03:11,149 --> 00:03:14,193
That guy, he burns me up.
那家伙，真是令我火大

51
00:03:14,736 --> 00:03:17,779
Yeah, well, it's a Mercedes if I move back home.
对，是宾士 只要我搬回家去

52
00:03:18,031 --> 00:03:20,949
It was horrible! He called me "young lady."
真讨厌！ 他还叫我〝小姑娘〞

53
00:03:21,201 --> 00:03:23,577
Ooh, I hate when my father calls me that.
我爸爸那样叫我时 我也很气

54
00:03:24,704 --> 00:03:27,956
Did he give you that whole "You're not up to this" thing again?
他是否又念些 〝你不可能办到〞之类的？

55
00:03:28,166 --> 00:03:31,168
Yeah, I got the extended disco version with three choruses of:
我听到的是加长版 有一句不断重复的副歌是…

56
00:03:31,377 --> 00:03:33,253
"You'll never make it on your own."
〝靠你自己是不可能成功的〞

57
00:03:33,504 --> 00:03:34,796
Uh-huh, uh-huh
哦 噢

58
00:03:38,343 --> 00:03:39,843
Hi, Joey.
嘿，乔伊

59
00:03:41,095 --> 00:03:42,262
Oh, my God. Angela.
哦，我的天！安琪拉！

60
00:03:42,472 --> 00:03:45,682
Wow. Being dumped by you obviously agrees with her.
哇！被你甩掉 对她显然是好事

61
00:03:45,934 --> 00:03:47,809
- Are you gonna go over there? - No.
- 你要过去吗？ - 不

62
00:03:48,603 --> 00:03:50,103
Yeah. No.
好，不

63
00:03:51,314 --> 00:03:54,233
Okay, but not yet. I don't wanna seem too eager.
可以，不过时候未到 我不想显得太饥渴

64
00:03:57,237 --> 00:03:59,863
One Mississippi, two Mississippi...
一下下、两下下…

65
00:04:00,281 --> 00:04:02,324
...three Mississippi. That seems pretty cool.
三下下 这样似乎就很酷了

66
00:04:06,704 --> 00:04:07,955
Hey, Angela.
嘿，安琪拉

67
00:04:08,164 --> 00:04:09,248
Joey.
乔伊

68
00:04:09,499 --> 00:04:10,707
You look good.
你看起来很性感

69
00:04:11,209 --> 00:04:14,253
Because I'm wearing a dress that accents my boobs.
那是因为我穿着一件 特别强调胸部的衣服

70
00:04:21,803 --> 00:04:22,970
You don't say.
可不是吗

71
00:04:24,847 --> 00:04:27,432
So, Rachel, what are you doing tonight?
那，瑞秋，你晚上有何计划？

72
00:04:27,684 --> 00:04:30,727
Big glamour night. Me and Monica at Launderama.
晚上可精彩了 我跟摩妮卡要去自助洗衣店

73
00:04:30,937 --> 00:04:32,062
Oh.
噢

74
00:04:32,772 --> 00:04:36,149
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence?
你想听一件诡异的巧合吗？

75
00:04:36,359 --> 00:04:38,193
Guess who's doing laundry there too?
猜猜还有谁也会去？

76
00:04:38,945 --> 00:04:40,362
- Who? - Me.
- 谁 - 我

77
00:04:41,155 --> 00:04:42,990
Was that not clear?
这样还不够清楚吗？

78
00:04:46,369 --> 00:04:47,661
Hey, why don't...?
何不…？

79
00:04:47,870 --> 00:04:50,998
Why don't I just join you both there?
我何不加入你们两个人的行列？

80
00:04:51,207 --> 00:04:53,667
Don't you have a laundry room in your building?
你住的大楼 不就有一间洗衣室？

81
00:04:55,336 --> 00:04:56,378
Yes.
对

82
00:04:57,714 --> 00:05:00,549
I do have a laundry room in my building.
我那里有一间洗衣室

83
00:05:02,552 --> 00:05:05,262
Um... But there's a rat problem.
不过，那里有老鼠出没

84
00:05:05,513 --> 00:05:08,724
Apparently, they're attracted to the dryer sheets.
他们显然对烘干机的芳香片 很有兴趣

85
00:05:08,933 --> 00:05:11,810
They're going in fine, but they're coming out all...
他们进去的时候都还好好的 出来的时候就…

86
00:05:12,520 --> 00:05:13,603
...fluffy.
蓬蓬的了

87
00:05:16,649 --> 00:05:17,691
Anyway, 7-ish?
总之，七点左右好吗？

88
00:05:18,026 --> 00:05:19,067
Sure.
当然

89
00:05:22,238 --> 00:05:24,323
Forget it, Joey. I'm with Bob now.
少来，我现在跟鲍柏在一起了

90
00:05:24,532 --> 00:05:26,867
Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
鲍柏？鲍柏是谁？

91
00:05:27,118 --> 00:05:28,493
Bob is great.
鲍柏很棒

92
00:05:28,703 --> 00:05:31,872
He's smart, he's sophisticated, and he has a real job.
他很聪明、见过世面 而且有正当工作

93
00:05:32,123 --> 00:05:36,043
You go on three auditions a month and you call yourself an actor. But Bob...
你一个月试镜三次 就说自己是演员，鲍柏则…

94
00:05:36,252 --> 00:05:39,296
Come on. We were great together.
拜托！我们在一起时很快乐

95
00:05:39,547 --> 00:05:43,925
And not just at the fun stuff, but, like, talking too.
不只是享乐的时候 比如说，谈话的时候也不错

96
00:05:47,305 --> 00:05:50,098
Sorry, Joey. You said, "Let's just be friends."
抱歉，你说过〝我们就当朋友〞

97
00:05:50,350 --> 00:05:51,808
So guess what?
你猜结果呢？

98
00:05:52,018 --> 00:05:54,144
- What? - We're just friends.
- 怎样？ - 我们就只是朋友

99
00:05:54,645 --> 00:05:56,063
Fine. Fine.
好吧，好吧

100
00:05:56,314 --> 00:06:00,067
So why don't the four of us go out and have dinner tonight? You know, as friends.
今天我们四个人 何不一块吃饭？就朋友嘛

101
00:06:00,318 --> 00:06:01,651
What "four of us"?
哪四个〝我们〞？

102
00:06:01,903 --> 00:06:05,364
You and Bob, and me and my girlfriend, um...
你跟鲍柏 我跟我的女朋友…

103
00:06:07,116 --> 00:06:08,158
...Monica.
摩妮卡

104
00:06:08,368 --> 00:06:11,286
JOEY: Monica, I'm telling you, this guy is perfect for you.
摩妮卡，我告诉你 这家伙很适合你

105
00:06:11,496 --> 00:06:15,290
Forget it! Not after your cousin who could belch the alphabet.
甭想！自从你那个打嗝天王亲戚后 我就不再相信你了

106
00:06:16,209 --> 00:06:20,045
Come on, this guy's great. His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
拜托，这家伙很棒 他叫鲍柏，他是安琪拉的…

107
00:06:20,296 --> 00:06:21,421
...ahem, brother.
兄弟

108
00:06:21,631 --> 00:06:23,673
He's smart, he's sophisticated...
他很聪明又见过世面…

109
00:06:23,925 --> 00:06:25,675
...and he has a real job.
而且他有正当工作

110
00:06:25,927 --> 00:06:29,846
Me, I go on three auditions a month and call myself an actor, but Bob is...
我一个月试镜三次 就说我是个演员，不过他是…

111
00:06:30,098 --> 00:06:31,681
- Oh, God, help us. - What?
- 老天爷啊 - 干嘛？

112
00:06:31,891 --> 00:06:34,267
Ugly Naked Guy is laying kitchen tile.
丑陋裸男在铺厨房地砖

113
00:06:36,020 --> 00:06:37,646
BOTH: Ew!
呕

114
00:06:38,147 --> 00:06:40,649
Look, I'm asking a favor here.
我是在请你帮忙

115
00:06:40,858 --> 00:06:43,360
I'm thinking if I do this for her brother...
只要我帮她兄弟这个忙

116
00:06:43,611 --> 00:06:45,445
...maybe Angela will come back to me.
安琪拉也许就会回到我身边

117
00:06:45,696 --> 00:06:48,990
What's going on here? You go out with tons of girls.
你干嘛？ 你的女朋友加起来有几卡车

118
00:06:49,200 --> 00:06:50,659
I know, but...
我知道，不过…

119
00:06:52,620 --> 00:06:57,124
Look, I made a huge mistake. I never should've broke up with her.
我犯了一个大错 我不该跟她分手的

120
00:06:57,333 --> 00:06:59,668
Will you help me? Please?
你帮帮我好吗？拜托？

121
00:07:06,050 --> 00:07:07,926
Okay. Bye.
好，再见

122
00:07:08,803 --> 00:07:12,389
Monica's not coming. It's just gonna be me and Rachel.
摩妮卡不去了 只剩下我跟瑞秋

123
00:07:13,766 --> 00:07:16,852
Hold on there, camper. You sure you've thought this through?
等等，你这黄鼠狼 你仔细思考过了吗？

124
00:07:17,103 --> 00:07:20,272
It's laundry. The thinking through is pretty minimal.
只是去洗衣服 不太需要用到大脑吧

125
00:07:21,399 --> 00:07:23,525
It's just you and Rachel? Just the two of you?
只有你跟瑞秋？ 只有你们两个？

126
00:07:23,776 --> 00:07:26,027
This is a date. You're going on a date.
这是约会 你们要去约会了

127
00:07:27,864 --> 00:07:28,989
Nuh-uh.
恩-啊

128
00:07:31,325 --> 00:07:32,576
Yeah-huh.
呀-哈

129
00:07:33,703 --> 00:07:34,870
What are you saying?
你觉得呢？

130
00:07:35,121 --> 00:07:37,539
I should shave again? Pick up some wine? What?
我该再刮一下胡子 或拿瓶酒过去吗?

131
00:07:37,790 --> 00:07:41,126
Well, you may wanna rethink the dirty underwear.
嗯，你也许需要 再考虑一下你的脏内裤

132
00:07:42,420 --> 00:07:46,548
It's the first time she'll see your underwear. You want it to be dirty?
这将是她首次目睹你的内裤 你希望是脏脏的吗？

133
00:07:50,887 --> 00:07:52,179
No.
不希望

134
00:07:53,639 --> 00:07:55,807
And the fabric softener?
还有柔衣精呢？

135
00:07:56,017 --> 00:07:58,810
Okay, okay. Now, what is wrong with my Snuggles?
好，我的柔衣精又碍到谁了？

136
00:08:00,396 --> 00:08:04,065
What? It says I'm a sensitive, warm kind of guy.
怎样？这代表我是一个 感性、温暖的男人

137
00:08:04,317 --> 00:08:06,776
You know, like a little fuzzy bear.
知道吗？就像一只毛绒绒的小熊

138
00:08:08,946 --> 00:08:11,364
I can pick something else up on the way.
我在路上再买别的好了

139
00:08:13,076 --> 00:08:14,862
（餐厅）

140
00:08:16,078 --> 00:08:17,078
MONICA: Thank you.
谢谢

141
00:08:17,288 --> 00:08:20,499
So what does this Bob guy look like? Is he tall, short?
这个鲍柏长什么样子？ 他是高还是矮？

142
00:08:21,125 --> 00:08:22,626
Yep.
对

143
00:08:23,419 --> 00:08:24,461
Which?
到底怎样？

144
00:08:24,921 --> 00:08:26,171
Which what?
什么怎样？

145
00:08:27,673 --> 00:08:29,799
You've never met Bob, have you?
你也没见过鲍柏，对吧？

146
00:08:30,009 --> 00:08:31,092
No, but...
没有，不过…

147
00:08:31,344 --> 00:08:33,720
For all we know, he could be horribly...
老天，这家伙搞不好长得很…

148
00:08:33,930 --> 00:08:35,136
Hey, Joey
嘿，乔伊！

149
00:08:35,806 --> 00:08:39,100
Horribly attractive. I'll be shutting up now.
很迷人 我不再多说了

150
00:08:44,148 --> 00:08:46,399
Where are they? Where are they?
他们人呢？人呢？

151
00:08:46,609 --> 00:08:49,945
This is nice. We never do anything, just the two of us.
太棒了，我们从来没有 单独做过什么事，就我们两个

152
00:08:50,571 --> 00:08:54,741
That's great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent a car, run over some puppies.
太好了，也许我们明天 可以租辆车去撞一些小狗

153
00:08:54,951 --> 00:08:56,493
Ew. I don't wanna do that.
我才不要

154
00:08:59,247 --> 00:09:01,998
- Here we go. - Have a good breakup.
- 开始了 - 祝分手顺利

155
00:09:03,751 --> 00:09:07,379
- Hey, Janice. - My God, I am so glad you called me.
- 嘿，珍妮丝 - 我的天，我很高兴你打电话给我

156
00:09:07,588 --> 00:09:10,840
I had the most supremely awful day.
我今天真是衰到家了

157
00:09:12,134 --> 00:09:13,468
That's not good.
那可不妙

158
00:09:14,929 --> 00:09:17,889
Can I get an espresso and a latte over here, please?
请送义式浓缩咖啡跟拿铁过来 好吗？

159
00:09:18,140 --> 00:09:21,059
We got the proofs from that photo shoot with the vegetables.
我们拿到那些蔬菜照片的样本了

160
00:09:21,310 --> 00:09:22,352
They sucked.
拍得很糟

161
00:09:22,562 --> 00:09:25,564
I blew off the rest of the afternoon. I went shopping.
我干脆下午翘班去血拼

162
00:09:25,815 --> 00:09:28,733
And I got you...
我给你买…

163
00:09:28,985 --> 00:09:31,945
JANICE: I'm looking. I'm looking.
我在找，我在找

164
00:09:32,363 --> 00:09:34,489
I'm looking.
我在找

165
00:09:35,199 --> 00:09:36,491
- I got you... - What?
- 我给你买… - 什么？

166
00:09:36,701 --> 00:09:40,412
- What? - What did you get me there?
- 什么？ - 你给我买了什么了？

167
00:09:40,705 --> 00:09:43,123
I got you...
我给你…

168
00:09:43,624 --> 00:09:45,000
...these.
买了这个

169
00:09:45,835 --> 00:09:47,752
Bullwinkle socks.
《鹿兄鼠弟》的鹿兄袜

170
00:09:48,004 --> 00:09:50,380
- That's so sweet. - I knew you had the Rockys.
- 真好 - 我知道你已经有鼠弟的了

171
00:09:50,631 --> 00:09:52,716
So you could wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle...
你可以穿鹿兄配鹿兄

172
00:09:52,967 --> 00:09:56,052
...or wear Rocky and Rocky, or you can mix and match.
或鼠弟配鼠弟，或混着穿

173
00:09:56,262 --> 00:09:58,138
Moose and squirrel.
糜鹿跟飞天鼠

174
00:09:58,347 --> 00:10:00,223
Whatever you want.
随你搭配

175
00:10:04,270 --> 00:10:06,938
I'm gonna get another espresso. More latte?
我还要一杯义式浓缩咖啡 你还要拿铁吗？

176
00:10:08,482 --> 00:10:09,691
No.
不用了

177
00:10:10,067 --> 00:10:13,153
No, I'm still working on mine.
不，我还在努力的喝这一杯

178
00:10:17,783 --> 00:10:18,825
That's it?
就这样？

179
00:10:19,076 --> 00:10:20,493
Yeah, it was really hard.
真的很困难 对

180
00:10:20,953 --> 00:10:22,871
Yeah, the hug looked pretty brutal.
那个拥抱感觉很残酷 对

181
00:10:23,539 --> 00:10:24,831
Okay, you weren't there.
你又不在场

182
00:10:29,629 --> 00:10:31,460
（自助洗衣店  自助或代洗）

183
00:10:37,720 --> 00:10:40,055
WOMAN: Coming through! Move! Move!
别挡路，让开，让开！

184
00:10:45,269 --> 00:10:48,647
Excuse me! I was kind of using that machine.
不好意思！我在用这部机器

185
00:10:48,898 --> 00:10:51,316
Yeah, well, now you're kind of not.
对，嗯，现在你好像没在用了

186
00:10:52,526 --> 00:10:55,403
But I saved it. I put my basket on top.
不过我已经有保留 我把篮子放在上面了

187
00:10:55,655 --> 00:10:58,114
- I'm sorry. Is that your basket? - Yes.
- 真对不起，这是你的篮子？ - 对

188
00:10:58,366 --> 00:11:01,368
It's really pretty. Unfortunately, I don't see suds!
很漂亮 可惜的是，我没看到洗衣粉！

189
00:11:03,913 --> 00:11:04,954
What?
什么？

190
00:11:06,123 --> 00:11:09,292
No suds, no save, okay?
没有洗衣粉就不能保留，好吗？

191
00:11:12,171 --> 00:11:13,630
- What's going on? - Hi.
- 什么事？ - 嗨

192
00:11:13,839 --> 00:11:17,592
Nothing. This horrible woman just took my machine.
没什么，那个讨厌的女人 抢了我的洗衣机

193
00:11:17,885 --> 00:11:19,344
Was your basket on top?
你的篮子有放在上面吗？

194
00:11:19,595 --> 00:11:21,805
- Yeah, but there were no suds. - So?
- 有，不过没放洗衣粉 - 那又怎样？

195
00:11:22,056 --> 00:11:23,556
You know, no suds, no save.
就是…没洗衣粉就不算保留

196
00:11:23,808 --> 00:11:25,767
No suds, no... Excuse me.
没洗衣粉就不…不好意思

197
00:11:26,018 --> 00:11:27,602
Hold on a second!
等一下！

198
00:11:27,812 --> 00:11:29,979
This is my friend's machine.
这是我朋友的洗衣机

199
00:11:30,231 --> 00:11:32,399
Hey, hey, hey! Her stuff wasn't in it!
嘿，嘿，嘿! 她的东西没放在里面

200
00:11:32,650 --> 00:11:36,653
Hey, hey, hey! That's not the rule, and you know it!
嘿，嘿，嘿! 你明知规矩不是那样的！

201
00:11:47,164 --> 00:11:48,707
All right. Show's over.
好，戏演完了

202
00:11:51,669 --> 00:11:53,878
Nothing to see here.
没什么好看的了

203
00:11:56,298 --> 00:11:58,466
Okay. Let's do laundry.
好，我们开始洗衣服了

204
00:11:58,676 --> 00:12:02,470
That was amazing! I can't even send back soup.
太厉害了！ 我连不是我点的汤都不敢退还

205
00:12:02,722 --> 00:12:07,225
Well, that's because you're such a sweet, gentle...
那是因为你是如此甜美、温柔…

206
00:12:09,562 --> 00:12:10,729
Do you, uh?
你有…？

207
00:12:10,938 --> 00:12:13,440
Oh, hey. You must need detergent.
哦，嘿，你一定需要洗衣粉

208
00:12:17,403 --> 00:12:19,362
- What's that? - Überweiss.
- 那是什么？ - 超白牌洗衣粉

209
00:12:20,322 --> 00:12:23,450
It's new. It's German. It's extra tough!
是新的，德国货 超强力！

210
00:12:25,536 --> 00:12:27,746
Rach, do you...? Are you gonna separate those?
瑞秋，你这些要分开吗？

211
00:12:29,331 --> 00:12:31,332
Oh, God. Ugh.
哦，天

212
00:12:31,584 --> 00:12:33,960
Am I being like a total laundry spaz?
我很洗衣白痴，对不对？

213
00:12:34,211 --> 00:12:38,047
Am I supposed to use one machine for shirts and another for pants?
我是否该把上衣跟裤子 分别放入不同的洗衣机？

214
00:12:41,594 --> 00:12:44,679
Have you...? Have you never done this before?
你从来没洗过衣服吗？

215
00:12:44,930 --> 00:12:48,057
Well, not myself. But I know other people that have.
哦，我是没有啦 可是我认识一些洗过衣服的人

216
00:12:49,852 --> 00:12:52,896
Okay. You caught me. I'm a laundry virgin.
好，被你逮到了 我是个洗衣处女

217
00:12:54,565 --> 00:12:57,609
Don't worry. I'll use the gentle cycle.
不要害怕 我会慢慢来

218
00:12:59,904 --> 00:13:00,987
Okay...
好吧

219
00:13:02,364 --> 00:13:05,950
Basically, you wanna use one machine for all your whites.
基本上，你得把所有白色的 放在一部机器里

220
00:13:06,160 --> 00:13:07,160
Whites. Okay.
白色的，好

221
00:13:07,369 --> 00:13:09,662
- A whole other machine for your colors. - Colors.
- 有颜色的放入另一部 - 有颜色的

222
00:13:09,872 --> 00:13:12,707
And then a third for your, uh...
还要第三部洗你的…

223
00:13:14,668 --> 00:13:17,337
...delicates. And that would be your bras...
贴身衣物 也就是你的胸罩…

224
00:13:17,588 --> 00:13:20,840
...and your underpanty things.
你的小内裤之类的

225
00:13:23,010 --> 00:13:26,054
Okay, well, these are white cotton panties.
这些是白色的棉质内裤

226
00:13:26,263 --> 00:13:28,765
Would they go with whites or with delicates?
是要跟白色的衣物放一起 还是跟贴身衣物呢？

227
00:13:29,391 --> 00:13:31,476
That would be a judgment call.
这得靠你自由心证了

228
00:13:36,649 --> 00:13:38,441
He's so cute!
他好可爱！

229
00:13:40,361 --> 00:13:42,070
So where did you guys grow up?
你们在哪里长大的？

230
00:13:42,321 --> 00:13:44,364
- Brooklyn Heights. - Cleveland.
- 布鲁克林高地 - 克里夫兰

231
00:13:44,573 --> 00:13:45,782
Ha. Heh, heh, heh.
哈 呵呵呵

232
00:13:46,033 --> 00:13:47,826
- How did that happen? - Oh, my God!
- 怎么会这样？ - 我的天！

233
00:13:48,202 --> 00:13:49,619
What?
怎么了？

234
00:13:50,120 --> 00:13:52,372
I suddenly had the feeling I was...
我突然有一种…

235
00:13:52,623 --> 00:13:54,207
...falling.
往下掉的感觉

236
00:13:55,543 --> 00:13:56,584
But I'm not.
现在没有了

237
00:14:06,887 --> 00:14:09,055
So you and Angela, huh?
你跟安琪拉在一起，是吧？

238
00:14:09,306 --> 00:14:11,516
Yep. Pretty much.
没错，就是这样

239
00:14:11,934 --> 00:14:13,393
- You're a lucky man. - Yeah.
- 你是个幸运的男人 - 是啊

240
00:14:14,520 --> 00:14:16,563
You know what I miss the most about her?
知道我最想念她哪里吗？

241
00:14:16,814 --> 00:14:20,066
That cute nibbley noise she makes when she eats.
她吃东西时发出的 可爱的小噪音

242
00:14:20,276 --> 00:14:23,361
Like a happy little squirrel...
就像一只快乐的小松鼠…

243
00:14:24,029 --> 00:14:25,697
...or a weasel.
或是黄鼠狼

244
00:14:27,116 --> 00:14:28,533
I never really noticed.
我没注意到

245
00:14:28,742 --> 00:14:31,160
Oh, yeah, yeah. Listen for it.
哦，有 有，你要注意听

246
00:14:32,037 --> 00:14:34,038
Monica. Monica is great.
摩妮卡 摩妮卡很正

247
00:14:34,290 --> 00:14:36,541
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
对，她是啊

248
00:14:36,792 --> 00:14:38,960
But it's not gonna last.
不过，不会长久

249
00:14:40,671 --> 00:14:43,006
She's too much for me in bed.
对我而言 她在床上需索太多了

250
00:14:44,216 --> 00:14:45,258
Sexually.
嘿咻方面

251
00:14:48,929 --> 00:14:51,806
I've gotta tell you, Bob is terrific.
我得告诉你 鲍柏超棒的

252
00:14:52,057 --> 00:14:53,349
Yeah, isn't he?
对，说的可不是？

253
00:14:53,601 --> 00:14:56,477
It's so great to meet a guy who's smart and funny...
能遇到一个聪明、有趣

254
00:14:56,729 --> 00:14:59,063
...and has an emotional age beyond 8.
成熟度超过八岁的男人真好

255
00:14:59,315 --> 00:15:02,817
You know what else? He's unbelievable in bed!
还有你知道吗？ 他在床上的表现让人难以置信！

256
00:15:05,029 --> 00:15:06,237
Wow!
哇

257
00:15:06,989 --> 00:15:10,033
My brother never even told me when he lost his virginity.
我哥连他几岁失去童贞 都没告诉过我

258
00:15:11,452 --> 00:15:12,493
Huh.
呵

259
00:15:13,203 --> 00:15:14,454
That's nice.
那很好啊

260
00:15:18,042 --> 00:15:19,452
（中央咖啡厅）

261
00:15:19,710 --> 00:15:22,670
You can do this. It's like pulling off a Band-Aid.
你可以的 就像扯下OK绷一样

262
00:15:22,922 --> 00:15:26,925
Just do it really fast, and then the wound is exposed.
动作快点 伤口就会露出来了

263
00:15:27,176 --> 00:15:28,676
Go! Go!
快！快去！

264
00:15:37,227 --> 00:15:38,770
Janice...
珍妮丝

265
00:15:41,607 --> 00:15:42,732
Hi, Janice.
嗨，珍妮丝

266
00:15:44,276 --> 00:15:47,820
Okay, here we go. I don't think we should go out anymore.
好，开始了 我想我们不该再交往下去了

267
00:15:50,658 --> 00:15:51,866
Janice.
珍妮丝

268
00:15:55,245 --> 00:15:56,621
All right.
好的

269
00:15:59,166 --> 00:16:00,333
Well...
好吧

270
00:16:01,293 --> 00:16:03,086
Well, there you go.
好，你说了

271
00:16:03,879 --> 00:16:05,505
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
停，停，停

272
00:16:10,135 --> 00:16:13,304
RACHEL: Okay, I know this is gonna sound really stupid...
我知道说来有点蠢…

273
00:16:13,555 --> 00:16:15,807
...but I feel that if I can do this...
不过我觉得 如果我今天能成功…

274
00:16:16,058 --> 00:16:18,935
...if I can actually do my own laundry...
如果我真的能洗我自己的衣服…

275
00:16:19,144 --> 00:16:21,020
...there isn't anything I can't do.
这世上就没有我办不到的事了

276
00:16:21,981 --> 00:16:24,357
That does not sound stupid to me.
我倒觉得 这句话一点也不蠢

277
00:16:24,566 --> 00:16:28,653
No, it's like... The first time I had to make dinner for myself after Carol left me...
卡萝离开我后 我第一次自己煮东西时…

278
00:16:30,072 --> 00:16:32,949
I'm sorry, that's all the time we have. Next on Ross...
对不起，我们的时间到了 下一次《罗斯秀》…

279
00:16:34,535 --> 00:16:35,535
Okay.
好

280
00:16:35,744 --> 00:16:36,953
- Uh-oh. - What, "uh-oh"?
- 啊哦 - 干嘛？

281
00:16:37,204 --> 00:16:38,329
Uh-oh...
啊哦…

282
00:16:38,539 --> 00:16:41,457
Uh-oh, the laundry's done.
啊哦，衣服洗好了

283
00:16:42,960 --> 00:16:44,627
It's a song.
这是一首歌

284
00:16:44,878 --> 00:16:46,713
The laundry song that we sing.
我们在洗衣服时唱的

285
00:16:47,756 --> 00:16:51,092
Uh-oh, the laundry's done
啊哦！衣服洗好了

286
00:16:51,927 --> 00:16:52,969
What's the matter?
怎么了嘛？

287
00:16:53,220 --> 00:16:54,303
Nothing. Nothing.
没什么

288
00:16:54,555 --> 00:16:55,888
The laundry's done
衣服洗好了

289
00:16:56,140 --> 00:16:57,223
Come on, show me.
得了，让我看

290
00:16:57,474 --> 00:17:01,561
It's just that you left a red sock in with your whites, and now...
只是你的白衣服里有一只红袜子 所以就…

291
00:17:04,273 --> 00:17:07,400
...everything's kind of pink. - Oh.
统统变成有点粉红的

292
00:17:07,943 --> 00:17:09,318
Everything's pink?
统统变成粉红的？

293
00:17:09,570 --> 00:17:12,321
Except for the red sock, which is still red.
只有那只红袜子例外 还是红的

294
00:17:12,781 --> 00:17:15,283
Don't be upset. It can happen to anyone.
别难过 这种事大家都会遇到的

295
00:17:15,534 --> 00:17:17,410
But it didn't. It happened to me.
可是这次发生在我身上

296
00:17:17,661 --> 00:17:21,247
God, I'm gonna look like a big Marshmallow Peep!
天哪，我会变成 - 只粉红凯蒂猫！

297
00:17:21,457 --> 00:17:23,291
What am I doing? What am I doing?
我在干什么？

298
00:17:23,542 --> 00:17:26,711
My father's right! I can't live on my own.
我爸爸说的对！ 我无法独立

299
00:17:26,920 --> 00:17:29,422
I can't even do laundry!
我连洗衣服都不会！

300
00:17:40,934 --> 00:17:42,810
Something went wrong with Underdog...
那个超狗气球出状况了

301
00:17:43,062 --> 00:17:45,271
...and they couldn't get his head to inflate.
他们又没办法帮狗头充气

302
00:17:46,607 --> 00:17:48,191
So anyway...
总之…

303
00:17:49,443 --> 00:17:52,236
...his head is, like, flopping down Broadway.
狗头就在百老汇上 直直滚下去，对吧？

304
00:17:53,363 --> 00:17:54,447
And I'm thinking...
我就在想

305
00:17:55,657 --> 00:17:58,409
...how inappropriate this is.
这真的是不对劲

306
00:17:58,786 --> 00:18:02,789
I've got something's in my eye. Joey, could we check it in the light, please?
我的眼里有东西 乔伊，我们到灯光下看看好吗？

307
00:18:06,126 --> 00:18:07,543
- Oh, my God! - What?
- 哦，我的天！ - 干嘛？

308
00:18:07,795 --> 00:18:10,505
Hello! Were we at the same table? It's like...
我们坐在同一桌吗？ 简直说是…

309
00:18:10,714 --> 00:18:13,007
...cocktails in Appalachia.
近亲乱伦

310
00:18:17,513 --> 00:18:21,682
- Come on, they're close. - Close? She's got her tongue in his ear.
- 他们很亲密 - 亲密？她的舌头都跑到他耳朵里了

311
00:18:22,476 --> 00:18:26,479
Like you've never got a little rambunctious with Ross.
你跟罗斯就没胡闹过

312
00:18:27,689 --> 00:18:31,400
Joey, this is sick. It's disgusting. It's...
乔伊，这很病态 很恶心、很…

313
00:18:32,236 --> 00:18:33,903
...not really true, is it?
这不是真的，对不对？

314
00:18:34,154 --> 00:18:35,822
Who's to say what's true?
谁晓得什么才是真的？

315
00:18:36,073 --> 00:18:37,156
What were you thinking?
你在想什么？

316
00:18:37,407 --> 00:18:39,951
Look, I'm not proud of this, okay?
这没什么好得意的，好吗？

317
00:18:40,202 --> 00:18:41,619
Well, maybe I am a little.
嗯，也许是有一点啦

318
00:18:41,829 --> 00:18:43,496
- Oh. - Ow!
噢 噢

319
00:18:43,705 --> 00:18:45,581
- I'm out of here! - Wait! Come on!
- 我要走了！ - 等一下！

320
00:18:45,791 --> 00:18:47,667
You like him. I want her.
你喜欢他，我要她

321
00:18:47,918 --> 00:18:49,335
He likes you.
他喜欢你

322
00:18:50,129 --> 00:18:52,004
- Really? - Yeah.
- 真的？ - 对

323
00:18:52,256 --> 00:18:55,967
I'm thinking, if we put our heads together, between the two of us...
如果我们团结起来 就凭我们二人…

324
00:18:56,176 --> 00:18:58,261
...we can break them up.
一定可以拆散他们

325
00:19:01,098 --> 00:19:03,516
MONICA: I'm so sorry. I can't believe I did this.
对不起 真不敢相信我会出这种差错

326
00:19:03,767 --> 00:19:07,228
I just couldn't stop laughing at your Norman Mailer story.
你那个作家诺曼梅勒的故事 让我笑到不行

327
00:19:13,569 --> 00:19:16,821
Waiter? One more plate of chicken wings over here.
服务生？我们还要一盘鸡翅

328
00:19:23,036 --> 00:19:25,496
Here's the thing. It's like we're different.
就像这样 我们根本不一样

329
00:19:25,747 --> 00:19:27,707
I'm the bing, you're the boom...
我是那种乒乒乒的人 你则是砰砰砰

330
00:19:27,958 --> 00:19:29,000
JANICE: Ow! - Oh!
哦 噢

331
00:19:29,209 --> 00:19:30,543
- Oh, my God!  - Ow!
- 哦，我的天！ - 噢

332
00:19:30,752 --> 00:19:31,794
- I'm so sorry! - Ow!
- 我很抱歉！ - 噢

333
00:19:32,254 --> 00:19:33,629
- Are you okay? - Ow!
你还好吗？

334
00:19:34,840 --> 00:19:36,883
It's just my lens. It's my lens.
只是我的隐形眼镜 我的镜片跑了

335
00:19:37,676 --> 00:19:39,135
I'll be right back.
我马上回来

336
00:19:41,513 --> 00:19:43,848
I hit her in the eye! I hit her in the eye!
我打中她的眼睛！ 打中她的眼睛！

337
00:19:44,099 --> 00:19:47,602
This is the worst breakup in the history of the world!
这是史上最差劲的分手！

338
00:19:47,853 --> 00:19:49,604
Oh, my God.
哦，我的天！

339
00:19:51,732 --> 00:19:53,191
How many of those have you had?
你到底喝了几杯？

340
00:19:53,442 --> 00:19:55,610
I don't know. A million!
我不晓得，一百万杯吧！

341
00:19:56,486 --> 00:19:59,739
Chandler, shh, shh. Easy, easy. Go to your happy place.
钱德，放轻松，放轻松 想想你快乐的时光

342
00:20:00,032 --> 00:20:02,158
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
啦-啦-啦-啦-啦-啦-啦

343
00:20:03,285 --> 00:20:05,661
- I'm fine, I'm fine. - All right.
- 我很好，我很好 - 好吧

344
00:20:05,871 --> 00:20:07,705
I'm not fine. Here she comes.
我不好，她来了

345
00:20:07,915 --> 00:20:09,749
Wait here, okay? Breathe.
在这里等好吗？呼吸

346
00:20:28,727 --> 00:20:30,061
How do you do that?
你怎么办到的？

347
00:20:30,312 --> 00:20:32,355
It's like a gift.
就像一种天赋

348
00:20:35,025 --> 00:20:37,360
We should always, always break up together.
以后我们一定要一起分手

349
00:20:37,611 --> 00:20:38,736
I'd like that.
我喜欢！

350
00:20:40,864 --> 00:20:43,991
ROSS: You got the clothes clean. That's the important part.
衣服干净了 这才是最重要的

351
00:20:44,201 --> 00:20:47,578
I guess. Except everything looks like jammies now.
我想也是 可惜现在全部看起来都像睡衣

352
00:20:53,252 --> 00:20:54,669
Whoa, I'm sorry.
对不起

353
00:20:54,920 --> 00:20:57,421
Excuse me. We had this cart.
抱歉，这推车是我们的

354
00:20:58,131 --> 00:21:00,841
I had a 24-inch waist. You lose things.
我的腰以前也只有二十四寸 人生总是有得有失

355
00:21:01,051 --> 00:21:03,344
Now, come on. Get out of my way.
好了，别挡我的路

356
00:21:03,595 --> 00:21:07,223
I'm sorry. Maybe I wasn't being clear. This was our cart.
对不起，也许我没有说清楚 这推车是我们的

357
00:21:07,516 --> 00:21:09,475
Hey, hey, hey. There aren't any clothes in it!
嘿，嘿，嘿! 刚才又没有衣服在推车里！

358
00:21:09,726 --> 00:21:12,311
Hey, hey, hey! Quit making up rules!
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿 不要乱订规则！

359
00:21:12,562 --> 00:21:15,940
Let go! Come on, this is my cart. You know I saw it first.
放手！快，这是我的推车 你知道是我先看到的

360
00:21:16,191 --> 00:21:18,401
Listen, Mitzi, if you want this cart...
给我听好，女人 如果你要这推车…

361
00:21:18,610 --> 00:21:21,153
...you're gonna have to take me with it!
就连我一起推走！

362
00:21:28,453 --> 00:21:30,329
Yes! Did you see that?
赞！你看到了没？

363
00:21:30,580 --> 00:21:31,789
You were incredible.
你太厉害了

364
00:21:31,999 --> 00:21:34,500
A brand-new woman, ladies and gentlemen.
各位先生、各位女士 看看这位全新的女性

365
00:21:34,710 --> 00:21:37,086
I could not have done this without you.
谢谢，没有你的话 我根本办不到的

366
00:21:43,468 --> 00:21:44,677
ROSS: Okay, um...
好

367
00:21:44,886 --> 00:21:47,805
Uh... More clothes in the dryer?
干衣机里还有衣服吗？

368
00:21:50,058 --> 00:21:52,184
- I'm fine. I'm fine. - Are you sure?
- 我没事，没事 - 你确定吗？

369
00:21:55,897 --> 00:21:58,190
- Are you sure you're okay? - Yeah.
- 你确定你没事？ - 确定

370
00:21:58,483 --> 00:22:00,484
- Does it still hurt? - Yeah.
- 还会痛吗？ - 会

371
00:22:03,113 --> 00:22:06,949
What a neat idea. All your clothes match. I'm gonna do this.
好主意！你所有的衣服都同色了 我也要这样做

372
00:22:08,744 --> 00:22:09,744
MONICA: Hi!
- 嗨

373
00:22:09,953 --> 00:22:10,995
PHOEBE: How'd it go?
- 还顺利吗？

374
00:22:11,204 --> 00:22:12,246
Excellent!
太棒了！

375
00:22:12,497 --> 00:22:16,751
We ripped that couple apart and kept the pieces for ourselves.
我们把那一对拆开了 然后各自保留一半

376
00:22:18,003 --> 00:22:19,337
What a beautiful story.
好浪漫的故事

377
00:22:21,840 --> 00:22:23,090
I'm fine, by the way.
对了，我没事

378
00:22:23,342 --> 00:22:24,675
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉

379
00:22:25,177 --> 00:22:28,095
- Where's Chandler? - He needed some time to grieve.
- 钱德呢？ - 他需要一点疗伤的时问

380
00:22:28,347 --> 00:22:30,598
CHANDLER: I'm free! I'm free!
我自由了！我自由了！

381
00:22:32,684 --> 00:22:34,268
That ought to do it.
应该是复原了

